<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="script.module.metahandler"
     name="metahandler"
     version="3.0.3"
     provider-name="Eldorado, jsergio">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.addon.common" version="2.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.myconnpy" version="1.1.6"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Downloads Artwork for TV shows, Movies and Music videos for addons and stores them in a local SQLITE database</summary>
    <description lang="en">Queries, stores, and returns metadata for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos. [CR]Sources:[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]www.imdb.com[CR]www.omdbapi.com[CR]This product uses the TMDb API but is not endorsed or certified by TMDb.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website></website>
    <email></email>
    <source></source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon
  id="webinterface.arch"
  version="2.0.5"
  name="Arch"
  provider-name="icolala">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.0.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.webinterface"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">A modern web interface for KODI</summary>
    <description lang="en">A modern web interface for KODI. Browse all your movies, tv shows and musics. See what's currently playing. Discover new movies and tv shows. All from your browser, desktop or tablets.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language>en</language>
    <license>The MIT License (MIT)</license>
    <forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=224515</forum>
    <source>https://github.com/abricot/webinterface.arch</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.simplejson"
       name="simplejson"
       version="3.16.1"
       provider-name="Bob Ippolito">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language></language>
    <summary lang="en">Simple, fast, extensible JSON encoder/decoder for Python</summary>
    <description lang="en">Simple, fast, extensible JSON encoder/decoder for Python</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Code taken from https://pypi.org/project/simplejson/</disclaimer>
    <license>MIT License, Academic Free License v. 2.1</license>
    <website>https://pypi.org/project/simplejson/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/simplejson/simplejson</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="visualization.waveform" version="3.1.2.1" name="Waveform" provider-name="MrC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.visualization" version="2.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.player.musicviz" library_linux="visualization.waveform.so.3.1.2"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Visualisering wat 2 golfvorm grafieke op die skerm vertoon</summary>
    <summary lang="ar">التصوير يظهر2 رسم بياني موجي على الشاشة</summary>
    <summary lang="be">Візуалізацыя што паказвае 2 графікі сыгналу на экране</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Визуализация представяща две осцилиращи вълни</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Visualització que mostra 2 gràfics en forma d'ona a la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Vizualizace zobrazující 2 grafy průběhu vlny na obrazovce</summary>
    <summary lang="cy">Delweddu'n dangos 2 Graff Ffurf Ton ar y sgrin</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Visualisering der viser 2 bølgeagtige grafer på skærmen</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Eine Visualisierung, die zwei wellenförmige Grafiken auf dem Bildschirm zeigt</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Οπτικοποίηση που εμφανίζει 2 Κυματομορφές στην οθόνη</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Visualisation showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Visualisation showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Visualisation showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Visualization showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Visualización mostrando 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Visualización mostrando 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Visualización que muestra 2 Gráficos de Forma de onda</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Visuaal, mis näitab ekraanil kahte signaalikujulist graafikut</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Kaksi aaltomuotograafia</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Visualisation affichant 2 graphiques de forme d'onde à l'écran</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Visualisation affichant 2 graphiques de forme d'onde à l'écran</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Visualización amosando 2 gráficos en forma de onde na pantalla</summary>
    <summary lang="he">חיזוי אשר מציג 2 גרפיים בצורת גל על המסך</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Vizualizacija koja prikazuje 2 valna grafikona</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Vizualizáció két hullámformával</summary>
    <summary lang="id">Visualisasi menampilkan dua grafik gelombang pada layar</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Visualizzatore che mostra 2 grafici di forma d'onda sullo schermo</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">画面に2波形グラフを表示するビジュアライザー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">두개의 웨이브폼을 보여주는 음악시각화</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Vizualizacija kuri parodo dvi garso bangas</summary>
    <summary lang="lv">Vizualizācija, kas attēlo 2 viļņveida grafikus uz ekrāna</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Визуализација која покажува 2 брана на екранот</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Visual di skrin menunjukkan 2 graf gelombang</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Visualisatie die twee grafieken in golfvorm weergeeft</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Visualisering som viser to bølgeformede grafer på skjermen</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wizualizacja pokazująca dwie fale dźwięku</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Visualização que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes no ecrã</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Visualização que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Vizualizare care arată 2 grafice Waveform pe ecran</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Визуализация, показывающая  на экране 2 волновых графика</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Visualisering som visar 2 vågformsgrafer på skärmen</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Vizualizácia zobrazujúca 2 grafy priebehu signálu</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Vizualizacija zvoka z dvema valovnima oblikama</summary>
    <summary lang="sq">Vizualizim që shfaq 2 Grafikë Valëzues në ekran</summary>
    <summary lang="sr">Визуелизација која приказује два таласна облика на екрану</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Visualisering som visar 2 vågformgrafer på skärmen</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">திரையில் 2 அலைவடிவம் வரைபடங்கள் காட்டும் காட்சி</summary>
    <summary lang="tg">Визуализатсия бо намоиши 2 нақши мавҷшакл дар экран</summary>
    <summary lang="th">กำลังแสดงผลภาพเวอร์ชวลไลเซชั่น 'Waveform' เป็น 2  กราฟสัญญาณบนหน้าจอ</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">2 Dalga Grafiğini ekranda gösteren görsel öğe</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Візуалізація показує на екрані 2 лінії, що змінюються в такт з музикою.</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Trình diễn đồ họa 2 đường sóng lên màn hình</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">在屏幕上显示两个波形图的可视化效果</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">在屏幕上顯示2波形圖的視覺效果</summary>
    <description lang="af">Golfvorm is 'n eenvoudige visualisering wat 2 golfvorm grafieke op die skerm vertoon, een elk vir Linker en Regter kanale wat beweeg op die maat van die musiek.</description>
    <description lang="ar">التشكيل الموجي هو تصوير بسيط يظهر2 رسم بياني موجي على الشاشة, واحد لقنوات اليسار و اليمين التر تتحرك على وقع الموسيقى</description>
    <description lang="be">Waveform is a simple Visualization showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen, One each for Left and Right channels that move to the beat of the music</description>
    <description lang="bg">Waveform представя графика на две осцилиращи вълни на екрана, по една за всеки канал (ляв и десен), който реагират на ритъма на музиката.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Waveform és una visualització molt simple que mostra 2 gràfics en forma d'ona a la pantalla, un per a cada un dels canals, esquerre i dret, que es mouen al ritme de la música.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Průběh vlny je jednoduchá vizualizace zobrazující 2 grafy průběhu vlny na obrazovce, které znázorňují levý a pravý kanál a pohybují se v rytmu hudby</description>
    <description lang="cy">Delweddu syml yw Waveform sy'n dangos 2 Graff Ffurf Ton ar y sgrin. Un yr un ar gyfer y sianel de a chwith sy'n symud i guriad y gerddoriaeth</description>
    <description lang="da">Waveform er en simpel visualisering, der viser 2 bølgeagtige grafer på skærmen. Én til den venstre og én til den højre kanal, der bevæger sig til musikkens rytme.</description>
    <description lang="de">Waveform ist eine einfache Visualisierung, die zwei wellenförmige Grafiken zeigt. Je eine Grafik für den linken und rechten Kanal, die sich im Takt der Musik bewegen</description>
    <description lang="el">Το Waveform είναι μία απλή Οπτικοποίηση του εμφανίζει 2 Κυματομορφές στην οθόνη, μία για το Αριστερό και μία για το Δεξί κανάλι οι οποίες κινούνται στο ρυθμό της μουσικής</description>
    <description lang="en">Waveform is a simple Visualisation showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen, One each for Left and Right channels that move to the beat of the music</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Waveform is a simple Visualisation showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen, one each for Left and Right channels that move to the beat of the music</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Waveform is a simple Visualisation showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen, One each for Left and Right channels that move to the beat of the music</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Waveform is a simple Visualization showing 2 Waveform Graphs on the screen, One each for Left and Right channels that move to the beat of the music</description>
    <description lang="es">Waveform es un sencillo visualizador que muestra 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla, uno para cada canal, derecho e izquierdo, que se mueven al ritmo de la música.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Waveform es un sencillo visualizador que muestra 2 gráficos de ondas en la pantalla, uno para cada canal, derecho e izquierdo, que se mueven al ritmo de la música.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Waveform es una Visualización simple que muestra 2 Gráficos de Forma de onda en la pantalla, uno para cada canal Izquierdo y Derecho que se mueven al ritmo de la música</description>
    <description lang="et">Waveform on lihtne visuaal, ekraanil on 2 signaalikujulist graafikut - üks vasaku ja teine parema kanali jaoks, mis mõlemad liiguvad muusika rütmis.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Waveform on kaksi aaltomuotograafia näyttävä yksinkertainen visualisointi. Toinen on vasemmalle ja toinen oikealle kanavalla ja ne liikkuvat musiikin tahdissa.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Waveform est une visualisation simple affichant deux graphiques de forme d'onde à l'écran. Chaque forme d'onde représente une voie, gauche et droite, et réagit selon le rythme de la musique.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Waveform est une visualisation simple affichant deux graphiques de forme d'onde à l'écran. Chaque forme d'onde représente une voie, gauche et droite, et réagit selon le rythme de la musique.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Waveform é unha Visualización simple que amosa 2 gráficos en forma de onde na súa pantalla, unha por cada lateral correspondente ás canles de audio da esquerda e da dereita que se move ó ritmo da música</description>
    <description lang="he">Waveform הוא חיזוי פשוט המציג 2 גרפים בצורת גל על המסך, אחד לכל ערוץ שמאלי וימני הזז לפי קצב המוזיקה</description>
    <description lang="hr">Waveform je jednostavna vizualizacija koja prikazuje 2 valna grafikona, po jedan za lijevi i desni kanal koji se pokreću u ritmu glazbe.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A Waveform egy egyszerű vizualizáció, amely 2db hullámot mutat reprezentálva a bal és a jobb hangcsatornákat, melyek a zene ritmusára mozognak.</description>
    <description lang="id">Waveform adalah visualisasi sederhana yang menunjukkan grafik dua gelombang pada layar, masing-masing untuk Satu saluran Kiri dan Kanan yang bergerak dengan ketukan musik</description>
    <description lang="it">Waveform è un semplice visualizzatore che mostra 2 grafici di forma d'onda sullo schermo, uno per il canale destro e uno per quello sinistro, che si muovono a ritmo di musica</description>
    <description lang="ja">Waveform は画面に2波形グラフを表示するシンプルなビジュアライザーです。音楽に合わせて、右チャンネル、左チャンネルの波形が表示されます。</description>
    <description lang="ko">Waveform은 간단히 두개의 웨이브폼을 화면에 보여줍니다. 각각 왼쪽, 오른쪽 채널이고 음악의 비트에 따라 움직입니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Waveform yra paprasta vizualizacija katra rodo dvi garso bangas ekrane. Viena banga vieno kanalo garsas.</description>
    <description lang="lv">Waveform ir vienkārša vizualizācija, kas atēlo 2 viļņveida grafikus uz ekrāna, vienu - labajam, otru - kreisajam kanālam, kas kustās muzikas ritmā</description>
    <description lang="mk">Бранови е едноставна визуализација која покажува 2 брановидни графови на екран, по еден за десниот и левиот канал од музиката</description>
    <description lang="ms">Gelombang merupakan visual ringkas yang menunjukkan 2 graf gelombang, saluran kiri dan kanan yang bergerak mengikut rentak musik</description>
    <description lang="nl">Waveform is een simpele muziekvisualisatie die twee golfvormen op het scherm toont, respectievelijk voor het linker- en rechtergeluidskanaal. De golfvormen bewegen mee met de beat van de muziek.</description>
    <description lang="no">Waveform er en enkel visualisering. Waveform viser to bølgeformede grafer på skjermen som beveger seg i takt med musikken. En for venstre og en for høyre lydkanal.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Waveform jest prostą wizualizacją pokazującą dwie fale dźwiękowe na ekranie. Każda na jeden kanał dźwięku.</description>
    <description lang="pt">O Waveform é uma visualização simples que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes no ecrã, um para cada canal estéreo. Estas ondas movem-se ao ritmo da música.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O Waveform é um visualizador simples que mostra 2 gráficos ondulantes na tela, um para cada canal estéreo</description>
    <description lang="ro">Waveform este o vizualizare simplă care arată 2 grafice în formă de undă pe ecran, câte unul pentru fiecare canal stâng și drept și care se mișcă după bătăile muzicii.</description>
    <description lang="ru">В этой визуализации отображаются 2 графика для левого и правого каналов, которые движутся в такт музыке</description>
    <description lang="se">Waveform är en enkel visualisering som visar 2 vågformsgrafer på skärmen, en för vänster och en för höger kanal som rör sig i takt med musiken</description>
    <description lang="sk">"Waveform" je jednoduchá vizualizácia zobrazujúca 2 grafy priebehu signálu pre pravý a ľavý kanál, pohybujúce sa v rytme hudby</description>
    <description lang="sl">Waveform je preprosta vizualizacija, ki prikazuje valovni obliki zvoka iz levega in desnega kanala, ki sledita ritmu glasbe</description>
    <description lang="sq">Valëzuesi është një Vizualizim i thjeshtë që shfaq 2 Grafikë Valëzues në ekran, nga Një për secilin kanal, të Majtë dhe të Djathtë, që lëvizin sipas ritmit të muzikës</description>
    <description lang="sv">Waveform är en enkel visualisering som visar 2 vågformgrafer på skärmen, en vardera för vänster och höger kanal som rör sig i takt med musiken.</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">திரையில் 2 அலைவடிவம் வரைபடங்கள் காட்டப்படும், ஒன்று இடது புற சேனலுக்கும் மற்றொன்று வலதுபுற சேனலுக்கு உரியதாகும்.</description>
    <description lang="tg">Waveform - визуализатсияи осонест, ки дар экран 2 нақши мавҷшаклро намоиш медиҳад, ду нақши алоҳида барои шабакаи чап ва рости ритми мусиқӣ</description>
    <description lang="th">Waveform เป็นการแสดงผลภาพเวอร์ชวลไลเซชั่นพื้นฐานที่จะแสดงกราฟสัญญาณเสียง 2 กราฟบนหน้าจอ โดยเป็นกราฟสัญญาณเสียงซ้ายและขวาตามจังหวะของเพลง</description>
    <description lang="tr">Dalgaformu, müzik vuruşlarına göre biri sol biri sağ kanal olmak üzere 2 dalga grafiğini ekranda gösteren görsel öğedir.</description>
    <description lang="uk">Waveform є простою візуалізацією що показує 2 осцилограми на екрані. Кожна лінія відповідає своєму каналу і змінюється в такт з музикою.</description>
    <description lang="vi">Waveform là một màn trình diễn đồ họa đơn giản hiển thị 2 đường sóng lên màn hình, Mỗi đường sóng sẽ đại diện cho một kênh tín hiệu loa trái hoặc phải di chuyển theo nhịp điệu của bài hát</description>
    <description lang="zh">Waveform 是一个简单的可视化效果，它在屏幕上显示两个波形图，分别与音乐左右声道的节拍相呼应。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">Waveform是一個簡單的可在屏幕上顯示2波形圖的視覺效果，左右聲道會跟著音樂節拍移動</description>
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-3.0</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/visualization.waveform</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/fanart.png</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="service.system.dispmanx_vnc"
       name="Raspberry Pi VNC"
       version="9.2.0.106"
       provider-name="Anton Voyl (awiouy)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="os.libreelec.tv" version="9.1"/>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>

  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="default.py">
    <provides></provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Raspberry Pi VNC: a Virtual Network Computing server for Raspberry Pi</summary>
    <description>
Raspberry Pi VNC (2018-08-18) is a Virtual Network Computing (VNC) server for Raspberry Pi using dispmanx
    </description>
    <disclaimer>

    </disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <news>
106
- Fix versioning

105
- Update to 5bde54b

104
- Force build against systemd

103
- Update to 77b33a6

102
- Build with Linux 4.7 RPi libraries

101
- Move settings to Kodi

100
- Initial addon
    </news>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>

    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.fanart.tv"
       name="fanart.tv Scraper Library"
       version="3.6.3"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="fanarttv.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="en">fanart.tv Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Scraper für Hintergründe von fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">fanart.tv taustakuvalataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">fanart.tv leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">fanart.tv-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Biblioteca de fundos fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обработчик Фоновых изображений с fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för fanart.tv</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">fanart.tv刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля декорации от www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download backdrops from www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Hintergründe von www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga fanart y fotos de artistas de www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa taustakuvia osoitteesta www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharge les backdrops depuis www.htbackgrops.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Fanartképek letöltése www.fanart.tv.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Achtergronden ophalen van www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj tła z www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar fundos de www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать фоновые изображения с www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner bakgrundsbilder från www.fanart.tv.com</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.fanart.tv.com下载背景图</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.favourites" name="Favourites script" version="7.1.3" provider-name="ronie, `Black">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="be_BY">Favourites script</summary>
		<summary lang="bg_BG">Скрипт "Любими"</summary>
		<summary lang="ca_ES">Script Preferit</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Script pro Oblíbené</summary>
		<summary lang="da_DK">Favoritscript</summary>
		<summary lang="de_DE">Favoriten-Skript</summary>
		<summary lang="el_GR">Script Αγαπημένων</summary>
		<summary lang="en_GB">Favourites script</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">Favourites script</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">Favorites script</summary>
		<summary lang="es_ES">Script de Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="es_AR">Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="fi_FI">Suosikit skripti</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_FR">Script Favoris</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Le script des favoris</summary>
		<summary lang="gl_ES">Script de Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="he_IL">סקריפט מועדפים</summary>
		<summary lang="hr_HR">Omiljene skripte</summary>
		<summary lang="hu_HU">Kedvencek script</summary>
		<summary lang="id_ID">Script favorit</summary>
		<summary lang="it_IT">Script preferiti</summary>
		<summary lang="ko_KR">즐겨찾기 스크립트</summary>
		<summary lang="lt_LT">Mėgstamiausių skriptas</summary>
		<summary lang="nl_NL">Favourietenscript</summary>
		<summary lang="nb_NO">Favorittskript</summary>
		<summary lang="pl_PL">Skrypt ulubionych</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_PT">Script de Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Script Favoritos</summary>
		<summary lang="ro_RO">Script Favorite</summary>
		<summary lang="ru_RU">Скрипт "Избранное"</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_SE">Favoritskript</summary>
		<summary lang="tr_TR">Sık kullanılanlar betiği</summary>
		<summary lang="zh_CN">收藏夹脚本</summary>
		<description lang="be_BY">Fetches item from your Kodi favourites to populate Home menu/submenu with custom buttons.</description>
		<description lang="bg_BG">Извлича информация от вашето меню "Любими" и показва допълнителни бутони в главното меню и подменюто.</description>
		<description lang="ca_ES">Obtenir els temes Preferits dels seus Kodi per omplir el menú Inici / submenú amb botons personalitzats.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Přenese položky z Oblíbených do Home menu/submenu pod vlastní tlačítka. </description>
		<description lang="da_DK">Henter elementer fra din Kodi-favoritter til at fylde Hjemmemenu/undermenu med brugerbestemte knapper.</description>
		<description lang="de_DE">Stellt die Einträge aus der Kodi-Favoriten-Liste für benutzerdefinierte Verknüpfungen auf dem Startbildschirm zur Verfügung.</description>
		<description lang="el_GR">Χρησιμοποιεί αντικείμενα από τα αγαπημένα σας του Kodi για να συμπληρώσει τα προσαρμοσμένα πλήκτρα μενού/υπομενού της Αρχικής Οθόνης</description>
		<description lang="en_GB">Fetches item from your Kodi favourites to populate Home menu/submenu with custom buttons.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Fetches item from your Kodi favourites to populate Home menu/submenu with custom buttons.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Fetches item from your Kodi favorites to populate Home menu/submenu with custom buttons.</description>
		<description lang="es_ES">Usar ítems de tus favoritos de Kodi para crear menús y submenús personalizados</description>
		<description lang="es_AR">Obtiene medios de sus favoritos en Kodi para enriquecer su menu inicio y sub carpetas con botones personalizados</description>
		<description lang="fi_FI">Hakee Kodin suosikeista kohteita ja populoi sillä Koti-valikon / alivalikon muokatuilla napeilla.</description>
		<description lang="fr_FR">Récupère l'élément depuis les favoris Kodi pour remplir le menu/sous-menu de la page d'accueil avec des boutons personnalisés.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Récupère l'élément de vos favoris Kodi pour remplir le menu d'accueil/le sous-menu avec des boutons personnalisés.</description>
		<description lang="gl_ES">Obtén o elemento dos favoritos para estabelecer botóns personalizados no Menú Principal/Submenú</description>
		<description lang="he_IL">מייבא פריט מהמועדפים שלך לאכלוס תפריט/תת תפריט עם לחצנים מותאמים אישית במסך הבית.</description>
		<description lang="hr_HR">Dohvaća stavke iz vašeg Kodi 'Omiljeno' izbornika i popunjava Početni izbornik/podizbornik s prilagođenim tipkama.</description>
		<description lang="hu_HU">Összegyűjti az elemeket az Kodi kedvencek közül és a központi menü almenüjébe helyezi egyedi gombokkal.</description>
		<description lang="id_ID">Ambil item dari favorit Kodi Anda untuk mengisi menu/submenu Beranda dengan tombol suka-suka.</description>
		<description lang="it_IT">Preleva elementi dai tuoi preferiti per popolare il menù principale ed i sottomenù con bottoni personalizzato.</description>
		<description lang="ko_KR">Kodi 즐겨찾기에서 항목을 가져와 사용자 설정 버튼으로 홈 메뉴/서브메뉴에 표시합니다.</description>
		<description lang="lt_LT">Paima elementus iš Kodi mėgstamiausiųjų, kad užpildytų pagrindinio meniu/submeniu individualiais mygtukais.</description>
		<description lang="nl_NL">Haalt item van je Kodi favorieten op om in het Home menu/submenu te plaatsen via losse buttons.</description>
		<description lang="nb_NO">Henter oppføringer fra favorittene dine i Kodi for å befolke hovedmenyen og undermenyen med egendefinerte knapper.</description>
		<description lang="pl_PL">Pobiera pozycje z twoich ulubionych w celu zapełnienia menu/podmenu niestandardowymi przyciskami.</description>
		<description lang="pt_PT">Obtém itens dos seus favoritos do Kodi para povoar o Menu Principal/submenu com botões personalizados.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Compila itens dos seus favoritos do Kodi para ocupar menus e submenus da tela inicial com botões personalizados.</description>
		<description lang="ru_RU">Извлекает информацию из Вашего меню "Избранное" и отображает дополнительные кнопки в главном меню и подменю.</description>
		<description lang="sv_SE">Hämtar objekt från dina Kodi-favoriter för att fylla ut hem-menyn med egna knappar.</description>
		<description lang="zh_CN">将 Kodi 收藏夹项目用于主界面菜单/子菜单的自定义按钮。</description>
		<disclaimer lang="be_BY">Needs skin support for it to be used properly</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Необходима е поддръжка от страна на облика за коректно функциониране</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ca_ES">Necessita Suport de la pell perquè sigui utilitzat correctament</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="cs_CZ">Pro správné použití je potřeba podpora skinu.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="da_DK">Behøver skinsupport for at blive brugt ordentligt</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_DE">Benötigt Skin-Support um korrekt genutzt zu werden</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="el_GR">Απαιτείται υποστήριξη από το κέλυφος για να χρησιμοποιηθεί σωστά</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_GB">Needs skin support for it to be used properly</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Needs skin support for it to be used properly</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_US">Needs skin support for it to be used properly</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_ES">Necesita ser soportado por el skin para poder funcionar correctamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_AR">Necesita soporte de mascara para ser usada correctamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Toimiakseen kunnolla, skinin tulee tukea tätä</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Nécessite le support du thème pour qu'il soit utilisé correctement</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Le prise en charge de l'habillage est nécessaire pour qu'il soit utilisé correctement</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Precisa da axuda da pel para que sexa utilizado correctamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="he_IL">להפעלה כראוי נדרשת תמיכה במעטפת</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Zahtijeva podršku presvlake za ispravno korištenje</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Felszín támogatás szükséges a helyes működéshez</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="id_ID">Memerlukan dukungan kulit untuk dapat digunakan dengan baik</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="it_IT">E' necessario che lo skin supporti lo script per funzionare correttamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ko_KR">스킨에서 지원해야 합니다</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Reikalingas teminės išvaizdos palaikymas tinkamam naudojimui</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Heeft skinondersteuning nodig om correct te werken</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="nb_NO">Krever skallstøtte for å fungere riktig</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Wymagane wsparcie skórki w celu poprawnego działania</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_PT">Necessita de um tema compatível para funcionar correctamente.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Necessita de suporte da skin para ser usado adequadamente</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ro_RO">Necesită suport din partea costumului pentru a fi folosit cum trebuie</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Необходима поддержка скинов для корректного отображения</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sl_SI">Potrebuje podporo preobleke, da bo uporabljeno pravilno.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Behöver skalsupport för att kunna användas riktigt</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="tr_TR">Düzgün kullanılabilmesi için dış görünüm desteğine ihtiyacınız var</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="zh_CN">正常使用需要皮肤支持</disclaimer>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=114671</forum>
		<source>https://gitlab.com/ronie/script.favourites</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.moviecountryicons.maps" name="Movie Country Icons - Maps" version="0.0.1" provider-name="braz">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false" type="moviecountryicons" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Map icons for the Countries node in Movies. Maps courtesy of DJAISS, https://github.com/djaiss/mapsicon.</summary>
		<description lang="en">Map icons for the Countries node in Movies. Maps courtesy of DJAISS, https://github.com/djaiss/mapsicon.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Requires implementation by skinner.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
		<forum></forum>
		<website></website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/braz96/resource.images.moviecountryicons.maps</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>screenshot.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.idna"
       name="idna"
       version="2.8"
       provider-name="Kim Davies">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Internationalized Domain Names for Python</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Packed for KODI from https://github.com/kjd/idna</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language></language>
    <license>BSD</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>https://github.com/kjd/idna</website>
    <source>https://github.com/Freso/script.module.idna</source>
    <email>freso.dk AT gmail.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.certifi"
       name="certifi"
       version="2019.9.11"
       provider-name="Kenneth Reitz">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Python package for providing Mozilla's CA Bundle.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Certifi is a carefully curated collection of Root Certificates for validating the trustworthiness of SSL certificates while verifying the identity of TLS hosts. It has been extracted from the Requests project.</description>
    <license>MPL-2.0</license>
    <website>https://certifi.io</website>
    <source>https://github.com/certifi/python-certifi</source>
    <email>freso.dk AT gmail.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="visualization.starburst" version="2.0.3.1" name="StarBurst" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.visualization" version="2.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.player.musicviz" library_linux="visualization.starburst.so.2.0.3"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">StarBurst visualizer</summary>
    <description lang="en">Frequency giving stars burst.</description>
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-2.0</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/visualization.starburst</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/fanart.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="vfs.rar" version="2.3.2.1" name="RAR archive support" provider-name="spiff">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.general" version="1.0.3"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.filesystem" version="1.0.2"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.vfs" version="2.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="kodi.vfs" protocols="rar" extensions=".rar|.001|.cbr" files="true" directories="true" filedirectories="true" encodedhostname="true" library_linux="vfs.rar.so.2.3.2"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="de_DE">Entpacker für .rar Dateien</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Unarchiver for .rar files</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Uppackare för .rar-filer</summary>
    <description lang="de_DE">Dieses Addon dient zum entpacken von RAR-Archiven.

Es ermöglicht das direkte Lesen nicht komprimierter RAR-Dateien, sodass ein vorheriges Entpacken nicht erforderlich ist. Bei allen anderen Typen wird es vorübergehend entpackt und an Kodi übertragen.

Achtung: Der Archivtyp "Solid RAR" erfordert ein vollständiges Entpacken, um die darin enthaltenen Dateien zu verwenden. Daher können die Zugriffszeiten für größere Pakete länger dauern.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">This addon is an extraction utility for RAR archives.

It allows direct reading of uncompressed RAR files, so prior unpacking is not necessary. For all other types, it is temporarily unpacked and passed to Kodi.

Attention: A "Solid RAR" archive type requires complete unpacking to use files within it. Hence access times may be long for larger packages.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Detta tillägg är ett uppackningsverktyg för RAR-arkiv.

Detta gör det möjligt att spela upp okomprimerade RAR-filer utan att de först packas upp. För alla andra typer, packas den upp tillfälligt och skickas sedan till Kodi.

Observera: Ett "Fast" arkiv kräver en komplett uppackning av arkivet. Därför kan uppstartstiden ta lång tid om det är ett stort arkiv.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Diese Version erfordert mindestens Kodi Leia 18.6; Bitte verwenden Sie 2.0.8 für frühere Leia-Versionen</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This version requires at least Kodi Leia 18.6; please use 2.0.8 for earlier Leia versions</disclaimer>
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/vfs.rar</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org"
       name="MusicBrainz Scraper Library"
        version="2.2.4"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="musicbrainz.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="en">MusicBrainz Music Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für musicbrainz.org</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">MusicBrainz musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper MusicBrainz pour la musique</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">MusicBrainz zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">MusicBrainz-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация MusicBrainz</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för musicbrainz.org</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">MusicBrainz音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.musicbrainz.org webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.musicbrainz.org</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.musicbrainz.org下载音乐信息</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.thecrew" name="[COLOR orchid]THE CREW REPO[/COLOR]" provider-name="The Crew" version="0.3.1">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension name="The Crew" point="xbmc.addon.repository">
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/thecrewwh/zips/master/_zip/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/thecrewwh/zips/master/_zip/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/thecrewwh/zips/master/_zip</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dobbelina/repository.dobbelina/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dobbelina/repository.dobbelina/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/dobbelina/repository.dobbelina/master/</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/therealatreides/housetools/master/code/_housefiles/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/therealatreides/housetools/master/code/_housefiles/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/therealatreides/housetools/master/code/_housefiles/</datadir>
		</dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="[login|startup]" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">The Crew is a team of individuals that does what it can to provide others, you the best in entertainment.</summary>
		<description lang="en">Many come, Many go. The true and dedicated are here. We here</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon do not host any of the content which is found and have no affiliation with any of the content providers. This addon simply searches websites for content. Use at your own risk!</disclaimer>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/art/ss/1.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/art/ss/2.png</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/art/ss/3.png</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database"
       version="5.2.2"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.imdb.com" version="2.9.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.themoviedb.org" version="3.2.6"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="4.4.10" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.movies"
             language="en"
             library="tmdb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">TMDB Fliek Skraper</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Сваля инф. за филми от TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Arreplegador de pel·lícules TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Stahovač informací k filmům z TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Crafwr Ffilmiau TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">TMDB Scraper til Film</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">TMDB Filmscraper</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Scraper Ταινιών του TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Scraper de películas de TheMovieDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper de Películas de TheMovieDB</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper de Películas TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">TMDB Filmi kaabits</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">TMDB elokuvatietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Collecteur de Films TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur de films TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Scraper de Filme de TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">TMDB סקרייפר סרטים</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">TMDB filmski sakupljač informacija</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">TMDB filmadat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Pengais Film TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">TMDB Skafa fyrir Kvikmyndir</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Ricercatore per TMDB Movie</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">TMDB映画のスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">TMDB 영화 정보수집기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">TMDB filmų skreperis</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">TMDB инфо за филмови</summary>
    <summary lang="ml_IN">മൂവി ഡി ബി, വിവരശേഖരം</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Pengikis Cakera TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="my_MM">TMDB Movie Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">TMDb-filmscraper</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">TMDB-skraper</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Ekstraktor filmowy TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Colector de filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper de Filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Scraper de filme TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Инфоресурс на базе TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">TheMovieDB filmový sťahovač</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Ponudnik informacij o filmih TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">TMDB Filmskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">LastFM நிகழ்படம் சுரண்டி</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">ตัวรับข้อมูลภาพยนต์ TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">TMDB Film Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">TMDB — джерело інформації про фільми</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Trình lấy dữ liệu Phim từ TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">TMDB 电影刮削器</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">TMDB 電影搜括器</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">themoviedb.org is 'n verniet en oop fliek databasis. Dit is totaal gebruiker gedryf deur mense soos jy. TMDB word huidiglik deur miljoene mense elke maand gebruik, en met hulle kragtige API word dit ook deur baie gewilde media sentrums soos Kodi gebruik om Fliek Metadata, Plakkate en Ondersteunerkuns te onttrek om die gebruiker se ondervinding te verryk.</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">themoviedb.org е безплатна и отворена филмова база данни. Задвижва се изцяло от потребителите си, от хора като вас. Милиони хора по света всеки месец ползват TMDb. Благодарение на многофункционално API може да се ползва от най-различни и популярни медийни центрове като Kodi, които извличат метаданни, постери и фанарт за филми с цел за красивото оформяне на интерфейса.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">themoviedb.org és una base de dades oberta i lliure. Es manté completament per usuaris, per gent com tu. TMDb s'utilitza actualment per milions de persones cada mes i amb la seva potent API també és utilitzada per molts centre media populas com l'Kodi per obtenir les meta-dades de pel·lícules, pósters i fanart per enriquir l'experiència d'usuari.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">themoviedb.org je bezplatná a otevřená databáze filmů a seriálů. Je celá řízena uživateli, tedy lidmi jako vy. TMDb je aktuálně používána každý měsíc milióny lidí a se svým výborným API je také používána mnoha oblíbenými multimediálními centry, jako je Kodi, k získávání metadat, plakátů a fanartů filmů a seriálů pro obohacení uživatelského zážitku.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mae themoviedb.org yn gronfa ddata ffilmiau rhydd ac agored. Mae'n cael ei yrru gan ddefnyddwyr fel chi. Mae TMDb yn cael ei ddefnyddio gan filiynau o bobl bob mis a gyda'i API pwerus, mae'n cael ei ddefnyddio gan lawer o'r canolfannau cyfrwng fel Kodi i estyn metadata ffilmiau, posteri a chelf er mwyn cyfoethogi profiad defnyddwyr.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">themoviedb.org er en fri og åben filmdatabase. Den er helt og aldeles brugerdrevet af folk som dig. TMDb bruges i dag af millioner af mennesker hver måned, og med deres kraftfulde API er den også brugt af mange populære mediecentre såsom Kodi til at hente metadata, plakater og fankunst til film, for at berige brugerens oplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">TheMovieDB.org ist eine freie und offene Filmdatenbank. Sie wird von Benutzern wie dir angetrieben. TheMovieDB wird zur Zeit von millionen Nutzern jeden Monat genutzt und dank ihrer mächtigen API ist sie auch von vielen Media-Center, wie z.B. Kodi, implementiert, um Film-Metadaten, -Poster und -Fanarts zu beziehen, die das Benutzererlebnis verbessern.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Το themoviedb.org είναι μία δωρεάν και ανοικτή βάση δεδομένων ταινιών. Διαχειρίζεται πλήρως από ανθρώπους σαν και εσάς. Το TMDb χρησιμοποιείται από εκατομμύρια ανθρώπους κάθε μήνα, και με το πανίσχυρο API τους, χρησιμοποιείται και από πολλά δημοφιλή κέντρα πολυμέσων όπως το Kodi για να λαμβάνουν μετα-δεδομένα Ταινιών, Αφίσες και Fanart για εμπλουτισμό της εμπειρίας του χρήστη.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Es una página web que se basa en contenido subido por los usuarios. TMDb es usada diariamente por mucha gente gracias a su API, que es usada por más programas aparte de Kodi para descargar información de películas así como Posters o Fanart (Fondos de escritorio basados en películas usados en distintos skins) para enriquecer la experiencia de usar Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Está  formada con contenido subido por usuarios como vos. TMDb es actualmente utilizada por millones de personas cada mes y, gracias a su poderosa API, es usada por muchos programas populares como Kodi para descargar Información de Películas, Posters y Fanart para enriquecer la experiencia de usar Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">themoviedb.org es una base de datos de películas gratis y abierta. Es completamente manejada por usuarios y personas como tu. Actualmente TMDb es usada por millones de personas cada mes, y dado a su poderosa API, es usada también por varios media centers populares como Kodi para obtener Metada de Películas, Posters y Fanarts, enriqueciendo de esta manera la experiencia del usuario.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">themoviedb.org on tasuta ja vaba juurdepääsuga filmide andmebaas.See on täielikult koostatud sinu sarnaste inimeste poolt. TMDb on hetkel igapäevaselt kasutuses miljonite inimeste poolt ja seda kasutavad paljud populaarsed meediakeskused, nagu ka Kodi, filmiandmete, fännikunsti ja posterite leidmiseks.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">themoviedb.org on vapaa ja avoin elokuvatietokanta. Se on täysin käyttäjien ylläpitämä. TMDb:a käyttää miljoonat ihmiset joka kuukausi, sitä käytetään käyttäjäkokemuksen rikastuttamiseen monissa muissakin suosituissa Kodi:n kaltaisissa ohjelmissa lataamalla elokuvien tietoja, julisteita ja fanitaidetta.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">themoviedb.org est une base de données gratuite et libre d'accès de films. Elle est totalement gérée par les utilisateurs. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et, grâce à ses puissantes fonctions et routines, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux Media Centers populaires comme Kodi aux fins de récupération des Métadonnées, Posters et Fanarts des films en vue d'améliorer l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">themoviedb.org est une base de données libre et ouverte. Elle est complètement gérée par des gens comme vous. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et avec son API puissante, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux centres multimédias populaires comme Kodi pour récupérer les métadonnées des films, les affiches et le fanart afin d'enrichir l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">themoviedb.org é una base de datos sobre filmes libre e aberta, impulsada por xente coma ti. Na actualidade TMDb é usada por millóns de persoas todos os meses, e grazas ó seu potente API, usado por algúns dos centros multimedia máis populares como Kodi para obter a información dos filmes, Posters e Fanart e así mellorar a experiencia do usuario.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">themoviedb.org je besplatna i otvorena baza filmskih podataka. TMDb trenutno koriste milijuni ljudi svaki mjesec uz pomoću njegovog snažnog API-ja, isto tako se koristi u mnogim popularnim medijskim centrima poput Kodi-a, kako bi mogli sakupljati informacije o filmovima, filmske postere, omote filmova i na kraju obogatili korisničko iskustvo.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">A themoviedb.org egy ingyenes és nyílt filmadatbázis. Teljes egészében olyan felhasználók töltik fel, mint például Te. A TMDb-t havonta emberek milliói használják és a hatékony API-n keresztül számos népszerű média center is, mint például az Kodi a filmadatok, poszterek, fanartképek letöltésére.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">themoviedb.org adalah database film yang gratis dan terbuka. Ini benar-benar digerakkan oleh orang-orang seperti Anda. TMDb saat ini digunakan oleh jutaan orang setiap bulannya dan dengan APInya yang digdaya, juga digunakan oleh beberapa pusat media seperti Kodi untuk mengambil Metadata Film, Poster dan Fanart untuk menperkaya pengalaman penggunanya.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">themoviedb.org er frír og opinn gagnagrunnur. Hann er algjörlega rekinn af fólki eins og þér. TMBd er notaður af milljónum manna í hverjum mánuði og með öflugum forritaskilum þeirra (API), er hann líka notaður af mörgum vinsælum heimabíókerfum eins og Kodi til að ná í Ítarupplýsingar yfir Kvikmyndir, Veggspjöld og Fanart til að lífga upplifun notandans.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">themoviedb.org è un database libero e aperto. E' gestito da utenti e persone come te. Viene usato correntemente da millioni di persone ogni mese e con le sue potenti API, è anche utilizzato da molti popolari media centers come Kodi per ottenere Metadati, Posters e Fanart di film per arricchire la loro esperienza utente.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">themoviedb.org は自由でオープンな映画データベースです。その運営は、完全にユーザ主導で行われています。TMDb は現在毎月何百万人もの人に利用されているほか、Kodi のようなメディアセンターも、TMDb のパワフルな API を介して映画メタデータ、ポスター、ファンアートを取得し、使い勝手を向上させるなどして使っています。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">themoviedb.org 는 전적으로 여러분 같은 이용자가 주도하는 무료 공개 영화 데이터베이스입니다. TMDb 는 현재 매월 수백만의 사람들이 강력한 API와 함께 사용하고 있을 뿐만 아니라 Kodi 같은 많은 미디어 센터가 영화 정보, 포스터, 팬아트를 가져와 풍성한 사용자 경험을 제공하는데 이용되고 있습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">themoviedb.org yra nemokama ir atvira filmų duomenų bazė. Ji palaikoma tokių pat vartotojų kaip ir jūs. TMDb šiuo metu naudojama milijonų žmonių kiekvieną mėnesį ir turi galingą API, o taip pat naudojama daugelio populiarių media centrų, tokių kaip Kodi, kad gautų filmų metaduomenis, plakatus ir Fanart, siekiant praturtinti vartotojo patirtį.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="ml_IN">മൂവി ഡി ബി, എല്ലാവർക്കും കൈവക്കാവുന്ന ഒരു സൗജന്യ വിവരശേഖരമാണ്. ഇതുമൂലം ലോകം മുഴുവനും സിനിമാ പോസ്റ്ററുകൾ എല്ലവരും കാണുന്നു</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">themoviedb.org adalah pangkalan data cakera terbuka. Ia sepenuhnya dipacu oleh individu seperti anda. TMDb buat masa ini diguna oleh berjuta-juta individu setiap bulan dan dengan API hebat mereka, ia juga digunakan oleh banyak pusat media popular seperti Kodi untuk mendapatkan Data Meta, Poster, Seni Peminat Cereka untuk memperkayakan pengalaman pengguna.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Themoviedb.org is een vrije en open filmdatabank. Gebruikers zoals jij vormen de motor van deze site. Op dit moment gebruiken elke maand miljoenen mensen TMDb. De krachtige API van de site laat mediacenters zoals Kodi toe om metadata, posters en fanart op te halen en zo de gebruikerservaring te verrijken.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">themoviedb.org er en fir og åpen filmdatabase. Den drives helt og fullt av mennesker som deg. TMDB brukes av millioner av mennesker hver måned og med sitt gode API, brukes den også av mange popluære mediasenterløsninger som Kodi for å hente metadata for filmer, plakater og fanart for å gi en bedre brukeropplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">themoviedb.org jest wolną i otwartą filmową bazą danych, zarządzaną przez osoby takie jak Ty. Obecnie odwiedzają ją miliony osób miesięcznie, a dzięki dostępności interfejsu programistycznego jest używana przez wiele centrów multimedialnych takich jak Kodi, jako źródło informacji o filmach, plakatów i tapet.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">O themoviedb.org é uma base de dados de filmes livre e aberta. É actualizado inteiramente por pessoas como você e usado por milhões todos os meses. Com o poderoso motor de busca disponível, também se tornou no favorito para muitos programas de centro de média, como o popular Kodi, para obter informação, posters e fanart que enriquecem a experiência do utilizador.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O themoviedb.org é um banco de dados aberto e gratuito. É completamente operado por pessoas como você. O TMDb é atualmente usado por milhares de pessoas a cada mês e com sua poderosa API, é usado por muitas centrais de mídia populares como o Kodi para buscar metadados, cartazes e fanart de filmes para enriquecer a experiência do usuário.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">themoviedb.org este o bază de date de filme gratuită și deschisă. Este actualizată de oameni ca și tine. TMDb este curent folosită de milioane de oameni în fiecare lună și datorită API-ului puternic, este de asemena folosită de multe centre media populare ca Kodi pentru a obține informații despre filme, afișe și imagini produse de fani (Fanart) care îmbogățesc experiența utilizatorului.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">themoviedb.org — это бесплатная и открытая база данных фильмов. Она полностью поддерживается обычными людьми. В данный момент сайт TMDb используют миллионы людей каждый месяц, и благодаря мощному API его могут использовать различные популярные медиацентры, такие как Kodi, чтобы получать метаданные, постеры и фанарт для фильмов с целью красивого оформления интерфейса.</description>
    <description lang="se">themoviedb.org är en fri och öppen filmdatabas. Det drivs helt av människor som dig. TMDb används av miljontals människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API, är det också använt av många populära mediacenter som Kodi för att hämta filmmetadata, omslag och fanart för att förgylla användarens upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">themoviedb.org je voľná a otvorená databáza filmov. Je výlučne vedená užívateľmi ako si ty. TMDb je každý mesiac používaná miliónmi ľudí, a vďaka svojmu výkonnému API je veľmi populárna medzi 'media centrami' ako Kodi pre sťahovanie filmových metadát, plagátov a fanartov pre obohatenie  zážitkov.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">themoviedb.org je brezplačna in prosta baza filmov. Je v celoti ustvarjena s strani uporabnikov kot ste vi. TMDB uporablja miljone ljudi in z njihovo močno API, jo lahko uporabljate tudi v multimedijskih centrih kot Kodi, s tem prenesete informacije o filmih, plakate in ozadja ter s tem popestrite uporabniško izkušnjo.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">themoviedb.org är en gratis och öppen filmdatabas. Den drivs helt av människor som du. TMDb används för närvarande av miljoner människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API används den även av många populära mediacenter som t.ex. Kodi för att hämta metadata om filmer, affischer och fanart för att berika användarens upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">themoviedb.org ஒரு இலவச மற்றும் திறந்த திரைப்பட தரவுத்தளம் ஆகும். இந்த தரவுத்தளம்  முற்றிலும் பயனர் மக்களால் இயக்கப்படுகிறது. TMDb அவர்களது சக்திவாய்ந்த API இனால் தற்போது பல இலட்சக்கணக்கான மக்களால் ஒவ்வொரு மாதமும் பயன்படுத்தப்படுகிறது, இது Kodi போன்ற பல பிரபல ஊடக மையங்களில் பயனர் அனுபவத்தை மேம்படுத்த பயன்படுத்தப்படுகிறது.</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">themoviedb.org เป็นฐานข้อมูลภาพยนตร์ที่ฟรีและเปิดกว้าง. มันถูกขับเคลื่อนจากผู้ใช้ โดยคนเช่นคุณ. TMDb ปัจจุบันมีการใช้โดยคนนับล้านในแต่ละเดือน และมีประสิทธิภาพด้วย API ของพวกเขา , มันยังถูกใช้โดยหลายศูนย์สื่อที่นิยมเช่น Kodi เพื่อดึง อธิบายข้อมูลภาพยนตร์, โปสเตอร์และ แฟนอาร์ต เพื่อเพิ่มประสบการณ์ของผู้ใช้</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">themoviedb.org ücretsiz ve herkese açık bir film veri tabanıdır. Tamamen kullanıcılar tarafından oluşturulmakta ve yönetilmektedir. TMDb her ay milyonlarca kullanıcı tarafından kullanılmakta ve güçlü API'si sayesinde Kodi gibi bir çok popüler medya merkezi tarafından Film Veritabanı, Poster ve Fanart bilgilerini kullanarak kullanıcı deneyimini zenginleştirmektedir.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">themoviedb.org - це безкоштовна і відкрита база даних фільмів. Вона повністю підтримується звичайними людьми. В даний момент сайт TMDb використовують мільйони людей кожен місяць, і завдяки потужному API, його можуть використовувати різні популярні медіацентри, такі як Kodi, щоб отримувати метадані, постери і фанарт для фільмів з метою оформлення інтерфейсу.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">themoviedb.org là cơ sở dữ liệu về phim ảnh mở và miễn phí. Nó hoàn toàn được kiểm soát bởi những người như bạn. TMDb hiện tại đang được sử dụng bởi hàng triệu người dùng hàng tháng và với sự hỗ trợ của bộ API mạnh mẽ nó cũng được sử dụng bởi những thiết bị giải trí cá nhân như Kodi cho việc lấy dữ liệu về Phim ảnh, Poster và Fanart để làm tăng trải nghiệm của người sử dụng</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">themoviedb.org 是一个开放和自由的电影数据库。它完全由象你一样的用户来掌控。TMDb 每月为上百万用户提供服务，并通过强大的 API 界面为许多流行的媒体中心系统如 Kodi 提供电影资料、封面海报和同人画以丰富用户的体验。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">themoviedb.org是一個免費和開放的電影資料庫。它是完全由與您一樣的廣大使用者來更新資訊。 TMDb目前擁有數以百萬計的使用人次並且有著強大的API，許多受歡迎的媒體中心平台像Kodi藉由TMDb獲取電影的數據資料庫，海報和影片資訊，以豐富使用者體驗。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=339672</forum>
    <website>https://www.themoviedb.org</website>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

    <addon id="repository.EzzerMacsWizard" name="EzzerMacs Wizard Repository" version="1.1.5" provider-name="EzzerMac">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="EzzerMacs Wizard Repository">
            <info compressed="false">http://www.ezzer-mac.com/_repo/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>http://www.ezzer-mac.com/_repo/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">http://www.ezzer-mac.com/_repo/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>

            <dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>

		<dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>

		<dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>

        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jenaddon/repository.jenrepo/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jenaddon/repository.jenrepo/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jenaddon/repository.jenrepo/master/zips/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>
        </dir>

		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/totalrevolution/python-koding/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/totalrevolution/python-koding/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/totalrevolution/python-koding/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>


		<dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary>Install all the latest Builds</summary>
            <description>Welcome to the New and Improved EZZERMACS WIZARD for all your Community Builds, All the Help and Assistance can be found Here</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.beautifulsoup4"
       name="BeautifulSoup4"
       version="4.6.2"
       provider-name="Leonard Richardson (leonardr@segfault.org)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python"
             version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Screen-scraping library</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Beautiful Soup is a library that makes it easy to scrape information from web pages. It sits atop an HTML or XML parser, providing Pythonic idioms for iterating, searching, and modifying the parse tree.</description>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <website>https://www.crummy.com/software/BeautifulSoup/</website>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.uisounds.amber" version="1.0.0" name="Amber UI Sounds" provider-name="Jester">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="kodi.resource.uisounds"/>
  <extension point="kodi.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Amber UI sounds</summary>
    <description lang="en">Amber UI sounds</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.arctic.horizon" name="Arctic Horizon" provider-name="jurialmunkey" version="0.5.47">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.14.0" />
        <import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.4.0" />
        <import addon="script.skinvariables" version="0.2.3" />
        <import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="0.0.5" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper" version="3.3.13" />
        <import addon="plugin.program.autocompletion" version="1.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.studios.white" version="0.0.10" />
        <import addon="resource.images.studios.coloured" version="0.0.19" />
        <import addon="resource.images.weathericons.white" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.moviegenreicons.transparent" version="0.0.6" />
        <import addon="resource.images.moviecountryicons.maps" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.arctic.waves" version="0.0.1" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension debugging="false" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1" point="xbmc.gui.skin">
        <res aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" height="1080" width="1920" />
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Minimal. Simple.</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Mínimo. Simple.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Arctic Horizon is a minimalistic skin with an emphasis on simplicity.</description>
        <description lang="es">Arctic Horizon es un skin minimalista con énfasis en la simplicidad.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial Share-Alike 4.0</license>
        <forum />
        <source />
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.jurialmunkey" name="jurialmunkey Alpha Repository" version="1.4-leia" provider-name="jurialmunkey">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="jurialmunkey Alpha Repository">
        <dir>
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jurialmunkey/repository.jurialmunkey/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jurialmunkey/repository.jurialmunkey/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jurialmunkey/repository.jurialmunkey/master/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>jurialmunkey Alpha Repository</summary>
        <description>A repository for alpha releases of jurialmunkey's skins.</description>
        <disclaimer></disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.thecrew.artwork" version="0.0.36" name="[COLOR orchid]THE CREW ARTWORK[/COLOR]" provider-name="The Crew">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">The Crew is a team of individuals that does what it can to provide others, you the best in entertainment.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Many come, Many go. The true and dedicated are here.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon do not host any of the content which is found and have no affiliation with any of the content providers. This addon simply searches websites for content. Use at your own risk!</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.bingie.helper" name="Bingie Helper" version="1.0.0" provider-name="cartman.dos">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<language/>
		<summary lang="en">BINGIE Helper Script</summary>
		<description lang="en">Helper for some of BINGIE features</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v3.0</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=334820</forum>
		<website></website>
		<source>https://github.com/cartmandos/script.bingie.helper/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.backgrounds" name="Skin Helper Service Backgrounds" version="1.0.34" provider-name="marcelveldt">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.13.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.metadatautils" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>

    <extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="login" />

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Helper service for Kodi skins providing rotating backgrounds</summary>
        <description>Helper service for Kodi skins providing rotating backgrounds</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<source>https://github.com/cartmandos/script.skin.helper.backgrounds</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.program.autocompletion" name="AutoCompletion for virtual keyboard" version="1.0.1" provider-name="Philipp Temminghoff (phil65)">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.autocompletion" version="1.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script"       library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">AutoCompletion for the virtual keyboard (needs skin support)</summary>
        <description lang="en">AutoCompletion for the virtual keyboard (needs skin support)</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.1, February 1999</license>
        <source>https://github.com/phil65/plugin.program.autocompletion</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.thecrew" version="0.0.95" name="[COLOR orchid]THE CREW[/COLOR]" provider-name="The Crew">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.thecrew" />
        <import addon="script.thecrew.artwork" />
        <import addon="script.thecrew.metadata" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" />
        <import addon="script.module.metahandler" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.crew.sports" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.3.3"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="thecrew.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">The Crew is a team of individuals that does what it can to provide others, you the best in entertainment.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Many come, Many go. The true and dedicated are here.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon do not host any of the content which is found and have no affiliation with any of the content providers. This addon simply searches websites for content. Use at your own risk!</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/art/ss/1.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/art/ss/2.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/art/ss/3.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="visualization.goom" version="2.2.3.1" name="Goom" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.general" version="1.0.3"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.visualization" version="2.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.player.musicviz" library_linux="visualization.goom.so.2.2.3"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="de_DE">Goom 2k4 Visualisierung</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Goom 2k4 Visualization</summary>
    <description lang="de_DE">Die Goom 2k4-Visualisierung unterstützt Effekte wie Tentakel, Blitz, Sterne, Feuerwerk, Wellen, Unschärfen und Glühen und enthält eine große Anzahl trippiger hypnotischer Effekte, die mit der Musik tanzen, wirbeln und knallen.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">The Goom 2k4 visualization supports effects like Tentacles, Flash, Stars, Fireworks, Waves, Blurs and Glows and includes a large number of trippy hypnotic effects that dance, swirl and pop with the music,</description>
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-2.0</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/visualization.goom</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.png</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.cdrepo" name="[COLOR deepskyblue]CellarDoorTV [COLOR white]Repo[/COLOR]" provider-name="[COLOR forestgreen][B]C[/COLOR][COLOR gold]D[/COLOR][COLOR ghostwhite]T[/COLOR][COLOR mediumblue]V[/B][/COLOR]" version="10.4">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension name="[COLOR forestgreen][B]C[/COLOR][COLOR gold]D[/COLOR][COLOR ghostwhite]T[/COLOR][COLOR mediumblue]V[/B][/COLOR] [COLOR ghostwhite]Repo" point="xbmc.addon.repository">
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/MrKoyu/repo/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/MrKoyu/repo/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/MrKoyu/repo/master/zips</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Gujal00/smrzips/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/teamuniversal/scrapers/master/_modules4all/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">CellarDoorTV Repository</summary>
		<description lang="en">[COLOR gold]The Future Of Home Entertainment[/COLOR][CR]Kodi Repository for [COLOR steelblue]CellarDoorTV[/COLOR][CR][COLOR forestgreen][B]C[/COLOR][COLOR gold]D[/COLOR][COLOR ghostwhite]T[/COLOR][COLOR mediumblue]V[/B][/COLOR] [COLOR white]Repo[/COLOR] allows you to install the CDTV WIZARD where you can get access to the latest CDTV Custom Builds and more.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.gif</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.studios.coloured" name="Studio Icons - Coloured" version="0.0.19" provider-name="Team Kodi">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="true" type="studios" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Coloured Studio Icons</summary>
		<description lang="en">Coloured Studio Icons</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.cherrypy"
       name="CherryPy Kodi module"
       version="11.0.1"
       provider-name="marcelveldt, CherryPy Team">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.9.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>CherryPy webserver packaged as Kodi module</summary>
        <description>CherryPy is a pythonic, object-oriented web framework
            CherryPy allows developers to build web applications in much the same way they would build any other object-oriented Python program. This results in smaller source code developed in less time.
            CherryPy is now more than ten years old and it is has proven to be very fast and stable. It is being used in production by many sites, from the simplest to the most demanding.
        </description>
        <license>BSD</license>
        <source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.module.cherrypy</source>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<!-- BINGIE -->
<addon id="skin.titan.bingie" version="1.0.3" name="Titan BINGIE" provider-name="cartman.dos">
	<requires>
		<import version="5.14.0" addon="xbmc.gui"/>
		<import addon="script.bingie.helper" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.6.5"/>
		<import addon="script.skin.helper.service" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.skin.helper.widgets" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.skin.helper.backgrounds" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.skinbackgrounds.titanium" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.skinicons.wide" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="resource.images.backgroundoverlays.basic" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
		<res width="1920" height="1200" aspect="16:10" default="false" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">BINGIE... The new Titan skin for Kodi Leia.</summary>
		<description>Titan is back for Kodi Leia with the new BINGIE layout!</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=334820</forum>
		<website>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=334820</website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/cartmandos/skin.titan.bingie/</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot000.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot001.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot002.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot003.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot004.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot005.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot006.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot007.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot008.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot009.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot010.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
		<news>
			[B]Titan BINGIE v1[/B][CR]Follow the forum thread about the latest news for the skin.[CR]https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=334820
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.toolbox" name="ToolBox Script" version="1.1.1" provider-name="phil65">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
	</requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script"           library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<language/>
		<summary lang="en">ToolBox Script</summary>
		<description lang="en">This script exposes several python functions to the UI engine as well as some other stuff to make life for skinners a bit easier.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2, June 1991</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=207618</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/phil65/script.toolbox</source>
		<email>phil65@kodi.tv</email>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="visualization.spectrum" version="3.0.4.1" name="Spectrum" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.visualization" version="2.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.player.musicviz" library_linux="visualization.spectrum.so.3.0.4"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Visualisering wys a roterende 3D Spektrum Analiseerder</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">عارض يظهر طيف محلل دوري ثلاثي الأبعاد</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Визуализация представяща ротиращ се 3D спектрален анализатор</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Visualització mostrant un analitzador d'espectre giratori 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Vizualizace zobrazující rotující 3D spektrální analyzátor</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Visualisering der viser en roterende 3D-spektrumanalyse</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Diese Visualisierung zeigt eine rotierende Spektrum Analyse in 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Οπτικοποίηση που εμφανίζει έναν περιστρεφόμενο τρισδιάστατο Αναλυτή Φάσματος</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Visualización que muestra un Analizador de Espectro giratorio 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Visuaal, mis näitab pöörlevat 3D spektraalanalüüsi</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Pyörivä 3D-spektrianalysaattori</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Visualisation affichant un analyseur de spectre 3D en rotation</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Visualización que amosa un analizador de espectro virando en 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">DirectX Spectrum זהו חיזוי אשר מציג סיבובי 3D Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Vizualizacija koja prikazuje rotirajući 3D spektralni analizator</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Vizualizáció 3D spektrum analizátorral</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Myndskreyting sem sýnir þrívíddar rófgreini</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">La visualizzazione mostra un analizzatore di spettro 3D rotante</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">回転する 3D スペクトラムアナライザーを表示する  ビジュアライザー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">회전하는 3D 스펙트럼 분석기를 보여지는 음악시각화</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Vizualizacija rodo rotacinis 3D spektro analizatorių</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Визуализација која покажува ротирачки 3Д анализатор на спектар</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">DirectX-visualisatie die een roterende 3D-spectrumanalyse weergeeft</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Visualisering som viser en roterende 3D ​​Spectrum Analyzer</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Wizualizacja pokazująca obracający się analizator widma w 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo em 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo em 3D</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Vizualizare cu afișarea unui analizor de spectru 3D rotativ</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Визуализация, показывающая вращающийся трёхмерный анализатор спектра</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Vizualizácia zobrazujúca rotujúci 3D spektrálny analyzátor</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Vizualizacija, ki prikatuje vrtečo 3D spektralno analizo</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Visualisering som visar en roterande 3D-spektrumanalysator</summary>
    <summary lang="th_TH">การแสดงแสงสี ทำให้เห็นการหมุนแบบ 3 มิติ ของการวิเคราะห์คลื่นความถี่เสียง</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Візуалізація що показує обертаючийся 3D спектроаналізатор.</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">显示旋转三维频谱分析图像的可视化效果</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">顯示旋轉的3D頻譜分析視覺效果</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Spectrum is 'n Visualisering wat 'n roterende 3D Spektrum Analiseerder, verbeeld met , vertoon wat op die maat van die musiek beweeg en 'n golf effek oor die spektrum rooster skep.
Dit het ook verstellings vir die aanpas van spektrum staaf hoogte, sy spoed, en hoe die stawe verbeeld word (solied, punte, draad raamwerk) en is 'n lekker ligte, lae cpu verbruik visualisering wat fantasties lyk</description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">طيف  هو تحليل بصري متحرك ثلاثي الابعاد للموسيقى! يتحرك بواسطة يرنامج  على وزن الموسيقى في شكل موجة.
توجد ايضا اعدادات لتعديل شبكة الطيف من حيث طول الاعمدة, سرعتها, وحتى شكلها (صلبة, نقاط, اسلاك) تعمل هذة بحمل خفيف, ومعالجة cpu ضئيلة لكنها تبدو رائعة</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in  that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.
It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Spectrum е визуализация изобразяваща ротиращ се 3D спектрален анализатор (рендването се извършва с ). Ротацията е според ритъма на музиката и предизвиква вълнови ефект по спектрална решетка.
Можете да настройвате височината на спектралните стълбове, скоростта и рендването - solid, points, wire frame. Характеризира се с отличен вид, като същевременно почти не натоварва процесора.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Spectrum és una visualització que mostra un analitzador d'espectre giratori en 3D renderitzat amb  que es mou al ritme de la música creant un efecte d'ona al llarg de la graella de l'espectre.⏎ També té opcions per ajustar l'alçada de la barra de l'espectre, la seva velocitat, i com es renderitzen les barres (sòlid, punts, malla de filferro). Una visualització que utilitza poca CPU i que és veu molt bé. </description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Spectrum je vizualizace zobrazující rotující 3D spektrální analyzátor rendrovaný v , který se pohybuje v rytmu hudby a vytváří vlnový efekt napříč spektrální mřížkou.
Obsahuje také nastavení pro přizpůsobení výšky sloupců spektra, rychlosti a způsobu vykreslení (vyplněný, body, drátový model). Je to velmi lehká vizualizace s nízkou zatíží CPU, která vypadá skvěle.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">-spektrum er en visualisering, der viser en roterende 3D-spektrumanalysator renderet i DirectX, som bevæger sig i takt til musikken og skaber en bølgeeffekt på tværs af spektrumfeltet.
Den har også indstillinger til at justere spektrumliniens højde, fart og hvordan den bliver renderet (fast, punkter, trådramme). Det er en letvægtsvisualisering med lavt CPU-forbrug, som ser godt ud.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Spectrum ist eine Visualisierung, die eine rotierende Spektrum Analyse in 3D zeigt. Die Visualisierung wird so gerendert, dass sie sich zum Takt der Musik bewegt und eine Welle über das Spektrum Grid legt.
Es lässt sich neben der Höhe, die Geschwindigkeit als auch die Art der Balken (durchgehend, Punkte, Drahtgeflecht) einstellen. Eine schöne Visualisierung, die nur eine geringe CPU-Last erzeugt</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Το Spectrum είναι μία Οπτικοποίηση που εμφανίζει έναν περιστρεφόμενο τρισδιάστατο Αναλυτή Φάσματος που αποδίδεται μέσω  και κινείται στο ρυθμό της μουσικής δημιουργώντας ένα κυματικό εφέ κατά μήκος του φασματικού πλέγματος.
Διαθέτει ρυθμίσεις για τον ορισμό του ύψους των στηλών του φάσματος, του τρόπου απόδοσης των στηλών (συμπαγείς, σημειακές, συρματόπλεγμα), και είναι μία ελαφριά, εμφανίσιμη και χαμηλής υπολογιστικής ισχύος οπτικοποίηση</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in  that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.
It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Spectrum es una visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando renderizado con  que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda en la rejilla del espectro.
Se puede ajustar la altura de las barras, su velocidad, y como son renderizadas (sólido, puntos, malla). Es una visualización que utiliza poca CPU y muy agradable.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Spectrum es una visualización que muestra un analizador de espectro en 3D girando, renderizado con , que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda en la rejilla del espectro.
Se puede ajustar la altura de las barras, su velocidad, y como son renderizadas (sólido, puntos, malla). Es una visualización que utiliza poca CPU y muy agradable.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Espectro es una Visualización que muestra un Analizador de Especto en 3D rotando renderizado en  que se mueve al ritmo de la música creando un efecto de onda a través del espectro de la red.
También tiene configuraciones para ajustar la altura de la barra de espectro, su velocidad, y cómo las barras son renderizadas (sólidas, puntos, malla de alambre) y es una buena visualización liviana, de poco uso de cpu que se ve genial.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">Spectrum on visuaal, mis näitab 3D spektraalanalüüsi renderdatud 'is, mis liigub liigub muusika rütmis luues laineefekti üle spektraalvõrgustiku.
Lisaks on olemas ka võimalus seadistada spektri kõrgust, selle kiirust ja kuidas ribasid renderdatakse (tahkis, punktid, sõrestik).  Spectrum on hea väljanägemisega kerge ja vähese protsessorikasutusega visuaal.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Näyttää pyörivän 3D-spektrianalysaattorin, joka liikkuu musiikin tahdissa tuottaen aaltotehosteen spektrikuvaajaan.
Spektripalkin korkeuden, nopeuden, ja piirtotavan (täytetyt, pisteet, ääriviivat) voi asettaa asetuksista. Spectrum on kevyt visualisointi joka näyttää hyvältä.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Spectrum est une visualisation affichant un analyseur de spectre 3D en rotation, sous . Il réagit au rythme de la musique, créant un effet d'onde sur la grille du spectre.
Il propose divers paramètres pour ajuster la hauteur, la vitesse, et le rendu des barres du spectre (plein, points, fil de fer). Une visualisation légère, peu gourmande en CPU et agréable à regarder.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Spectrum é unha Visualización que amosa un analizador de espectro virando en 3D renderizado con  que se move ó ritmo da música creando un efecto de onde ó longo da grella do espectro.
Tamén ten opcións para axustar a altura da barra, a velocidade e como se renderizan as barras (sólidas, puntos, malla) do espectro. É bonito, lixeiro, de baixo custo en CPU.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">Spectrum זהו חיזוי אשר מציג סיבובי 3D Spectrum Analyzer אשר זז לצלילי המוזיקה שיוצר אפקט גלים לרוחב רשת הספקטרום.
יש אפשרות גם להגדיר את גובה פס הספקטרום, את המהירות, ואת התנהגות הפסים (filled, points, wire frame) וזהו חיזוי נחמד קל משקל לא מעמיס על המעבד ונראה נהדר.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Spectrum je vizualizacija koja prikazuje rotirajući 3D spektralni analizator renderiran u -u koji se pokreće u ritmu muzike stvarajući efekt valova u spektralnoj mreži.
Također sadrži i postavke za namještanje visine sprektralnih traka, njihove brzine, i načina na koji su prikazane (popunjeno, točke, žičani okvir). Vizualizacija izgleda sjajno te je malih memorijskih i CPU zahtjeva.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Az Spectrum egy olyan vizualizáció ami egy 3D hang spektrum analizátort mutat  segítségével megjelenítve, ami a zene ritmusára mozog egy hullám-effektust képezve a teljes spektrumhálón.
Beállítható a spektrum oszlopok magassága, mozgási sebessége és hogy az oszlopok hogyan jelenjenek meg (teli, pontok, drótváz). Ez egy kis erőforrásigényű vizualizáció ami nagyon jól mutat.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Spectrum er myndskreyting sem sýnir þrívíddar rófgreini sem snýst sem er teiknaður í  og hreyfist í takt við tónlistina sem myndar bylgjuhreyfingu yfir rófið.
Það er líka hægt að stilla hæð mælingana, hraða og hvernig þær eru teiknaðar (fyllt, punktar, útlínur) myndskrytingin setur lítið álag á örgjörva og lítur vel út</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Spectrum è una visualizzazione che mostra un analizzatore di spettro renderizzato in  che si muove a tempo di musica creando un effetto onda attraverso la griglia.
E' possibile regolare varie impostazioni: l'altezza delle barre, la velocità di risposta e come le barre sono renderizzate (piene, con punti o con righe). E' una visualizzazione rilassante e con basso uso del processore.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in  that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.
It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">스펙트럼은 회전하는 3D 스펙트럼 분석기를 통해 음악시각화를 보여주며 음악의 비트가 만들어내는 웨이브 효과를 스펙트럼 그리드에 보여줍니다. 설정에서 스펙트럼 바의 높이, 속도, 바의 갯수 (채워짐, 점, 와이어 프레임)를 지정할수 있습니다. 가볍고 CPU를 많이 사용하지 않습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Spektro vizualizacija, kurioje besisukantį 3D spektro analizatorių, priimtą , katras juda į muzikos ritmą, įsteigiantis bangų poveikį visame spektro tinklelyje.
Taip pat turi nustatymus nureguliuoti spektro juostos aukštį, jos greitį, ir teikiamas kraštines (kieta, taškai, tinklelio rėmas) ir yra gražus bei lengvas, mažai naudoja CPU vizualizacijai, ir atrodo puikiai</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">Spectrum is a Visualisation showing a rotating 3D Spectrum Analyzer rendered in  that moves to the beat of the music creating a wave effect across the spectrum grid.⏎ It also has settings to adjust the spectrum bar height, Its speed, and how the bars are rendered (solid, points, wire frame) and is a nice light weight, low cpu useage visualisation that looks great</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Spectrum is een visualisatie met een draaiende 3D ​​Spectrum Analyzer gerenderd in . Deze visualisatie beweegt op het ritme van de muziek en creëert een golf effect over het hele spectrum. ⏎
Het heeft instellingen om de barhoogte en de snelheid aan te passen, en hoe de staven worden weergegeven (vast, punten, draad frame) en is een mooie lichtgewicht visualisatie die weinig van de cpu vraagt en er geweldig uit ziet.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Spectrum er en visualisering som viser et roterende 3D ​​Spectrum Analyzer gjengitt i  som flytter til rytmen i musikken skaper en bølge effekt over hele spekteret rutenettet.⏎
Det har også innstillinger for å justere spekterets bar høyde, hastighet, og hvordan barene gjengis (solid, punkt, wireframe) og er en fin lett vekt, lav cpu brukende visualisering som ser flott ut</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Wizualizacja pokazuje obracający się, trójwymiarowy analizator widma, renderowany przy użyciu . Możesz ustawić wysokość słupków, ich prędkość i wygląd.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Spectrum é uma visualização que mostra um analisador espectral 3D rotativo, renderizado em , que se sincroniza com o ritmo da música, criando assim um efeito de ondas na grelha espectral.
Pode-se definir a altura das barras, a sua velocidade e como são renderizadas (sólido, pontos ou contorno). É uma visualização que não utiliza muito CPU e tem um aspecto fantástico.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O Spectrum é uma visualização que mostra um analisador espectral rotativo 3D, renderizado em , que se sincroniza com a batida, criando assim um efeito de ondas na grelha espectral.
Pode-se definir a altura das barras, a sua velocidade e como são renderizadas (sólido, pontos ou contorno). É uma visualização que utiliza pouco o CPU e com um visual fantástico.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Spectrul  este o vizualizare care afișează un analizor de spectre 3D rotativ randat în  care se mișcă după bătăile muzicii creând un val dea-lungul grilei spectrale.
De asemenea, are setări pentru ajustarea înălțimii bărilor spectrale, a vitezei, și a modului în care bările sunt randate (umplere, puncte, contur). Este o vizualizare cu consum redus al procesorului care arată fantastic de bine.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Эта визуализация на основе  показывает вращающийся трёхмерный анализатор спектра, который движется в такт музыке, создавая эффект волны по всему спектру сетки.⏎
Визуализация имеет настройки для регулировки высоты полос спектра, скорости движения и способа отображения полос (сплошной, точки, каркас), а также обладает небольшим размером и малой нагрузкой на процессор.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Spectrum je vizualizácia zobrazujúca rotujúci 3D spektrálny analyzátor vykresľovaný pomocou , ktorý sa hýbe v rytme hudby a tak vytvára vlny naprieč mriežkou spektra.[CR]
Zároveň má nastavenia upravujúce výšku stĺpcov spektra, ich rýchlosť a ako sú vykresľované (vyplnené, body, drôtový model). Je to jednoduchá vizualizácia s nízkou záťažou CPU, ktorá výborne vyzerá.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Spectrum je vizualizacija, ki prikazuje vrtečo 3D spektralno analizato, generirano v , ki se premika v ritmu glasbe in ustvarja učinek valovanja v celotnem spektru. Vsebuje tudi nastavitve za prilagoditev višine spektra, hitrosti in oblike (polno, točke, okvir) ter je varčna vizualizacija z nizka porabo CPU-ja, ki izgleda super.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Spektrum är en visualisering som visar en roterande 3D-spektrumanalysator renderad i . Den rör sig till musikens takt och skapar en vågeffekt över spektrat.
-spektrum har inställningar för att justera staplarnas höjd, deras hastighet, hur de ska visas (solida, punkter, ramverk) och är en visualisering med låg cpu-användning samtidigt som den ser bra ut</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">Spectrum เป็น การแสดงแสงสี ทำให้เห็นการหมุนกราฟวิเคราะห์คลื่นความถี่เสียง แบบ 3 มิติ ที่สร้างขึ้นโดย  ที่ขยับไปตามจังหวะของเพลงที่สร้างผลกระทบเป็นคลื่นไปทั่วตารางความถี่.
นอกจากนี้ยังมีการตั้งค่าเพื่อปรับความสูงของแท่งคลื่นความถี่,ความเร็วและกระบวนการที่แท่งแสดงผล (ของแข็ง, จุด, โครงลวด) ทั้งยังใช้ทรัพยากรน้อยได้ดี, การแสดงแสงสี ที่ใช้ซีพียูต่ำนั่นก็ดูยอดเยี่ยมทีเดียว</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Spectrum  є візалізаціє що показує обертаючийся 3D спектроаналізатор що промальовується з використанням технології  . Спектроаналізатор показує стовпчики змінної висоти що рухаються в такт з музикою і створюють ефект подібний до хвилі.
Ви маєте можливість налаштувати висоту стовпчиків, їх швидкість і те як вони намальовані (Заповнені, контури, крапки). Це досить проста, і невимоглива до процесора візуалізація, але яка має чудовий вигляд.</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">Spectrum可视化效果是渲染的一个旋转的三维频谱分析图像，频谱矩阵随着音乐节拍而象波浪起伏。
你还可以设置频谱棒的高度、变换速度、以及呈现效果（固体、点、框架）。这是一个不错的轻量级，低CPU使用率的可视化效果。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW"> Spectrum 是使用  描繪顯示旋轉的3D頻譜分析視覺效果，頻譜格線隨著音樂節拍而像波浪起伏。
它還可以調整頻譜長條的高度、速度以及呈現效果（實心、點狀、線框）。它是個很好的輕量級、低 CPU 使用率的視覺化效果。</description>
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-2.0</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/visualization.spectrum</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.simplecache" name="Simple Cache Module" version="1.0.18" provider-name="marcelveldt">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Provides a simple file- and memory based cache for Kodi addons</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Provides a simple file- and memory based cache for Kodi addons</description>
	    <news>v1.0.18 (2019-12-23)[CR]- small fixes[CR][CR]v1.0.17 (2019-08-16)[CR]- Python 2/3 compatiblity[CR][CR]v1.0.16 (2018-03-30)[CR]- Final update from marcelveldt</news>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Apache 2.0</license>
        <forum/>
        <source>https://github.com/kodi-community-addons/script.module.simplecache</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.addon.common"
	     name="Common addon methods"
	     version="2.0.0"
	     provider-name="Eldorado (original: t0mm0)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines</summary>
    <description lang="en">Collection of commonly used addon routines to simplify addon development.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en"></disclaimer>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website></website>
    <email></email>
    <source></source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.resolveurl" name="ResolveURL" version="5.1.11" provider-name="gujal">
    <requires>
        <!-- <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" /> -->
        <import addon="script.module.six" version="0.0.1"/>
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.python.twitch" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.module.cryptopy" version="1.2.6" optional="true" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.gdrive" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="lib/default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Resolver enlaces a videos de sitios populares para poder reproducirlos en XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <summary lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju.</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi.</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">Resolve common video host URL's to be playable in XBMC/Kodi, simplify addon development of video plugins requiring multi video hosts.</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Επίλυση συνδέσμων κοινών εξυπηρετητών σε μορφή βίντεο ικανό για αναπαραγωγή στο XBMC/Kodi, απλοποίηση της ανάπτυξης των προσθέτων που χρησιμοποιούν πολλαπλούς εξυπηρετητές για υλικό βίντεο</description>
        <description lang="hr_HR">Prilagodi najčešće URL-ove video izvora kako bi radili u XBMC/Kodiju, pojednostavnjuje razvoj priključaka za video dodatke koji zahtjevaju višestruke video izvore.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This script only resolves video content from legitimate file lockers without prejudice. If this script is being used by 3rd parties to resolve content that you feel infringes upon your Intellectual Property then please take your complaints to the actual website or developer linking to such content and not here. This script in no way searches for any content whatsoever.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Το ανωτέρο σενάριο το μόνο που κάνει είναι να επιλύει οπτικοακουστικό περιεχόμενο από νόμιμες πηγές χωρίς προκατάληψη. Εάν το ανωτέρο σενάριο χρησιμοποιηθεί από τρίτους ώστε να επιλύσει περιεχόμενο το οποίο σας προκαλεί αντίδραση ότι παραβιάζει την πνευματική σας ιδιοκτησία παρακαλώ μεταφέρετε τα παραπονά σας στον ιστότοπο τον οποίο βρίσκεται το εν λόγω περιεχόμενο η τον δημιουργό ο οποίος πραγματοποιεί την σύνδεση και όχι εδω. Το σενάριο αυτό ουδεμία περίπτωση πραγματοποιεί αναζήτηση περιεχομένου.</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.backports.functools_lru_cache"
       name="backports.functools_lru_cache"
       version="1.6.1"
       provider-name="Jason R. Coombs">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Backport of functools.lru_cache from Python 3.3</summary>
    <description lang="en">Packed for Kodi from https://github.com/jaraco/backports.functools_lru_cache</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://github.com/jaraco/backports.functools_lru_cache</website>
    <source>https://github.com/Razzeee/script.module.backports.functools_lru_cache</source>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.musicbrainz"
       name="Musicbrainz NGS webservice python bindings"
       version="0.6.0"
       provider-name="marcelveldt">
  <requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>Python bindings for Musicbrainz' NGS webservice</summary>
    <description>Kodi module library for the Python bindings for Musicbrainz' NGS webservice developed by alastair.</description>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
    <source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.module.musicbrainz</source>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.autocompletion" name="AutoCompletion library" version="1.1.2" provider-name="Philipp Temminghoff (phil65)">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Module providing some AutoCompletion functions</summary>
        <description lang="en">Module providing some AutoCompletion functions</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.1, February 1999</license>
        <source>https://github.com/phil65/script.module.autocompletion</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper"
version="3.3.21"
name="TheMovieDb Helper"
provider-name="jurialmunkey">
<requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
  <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.11" />
  <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
  <import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
  <provides>video</provides>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py" />
<extension point="kodi.context.item">
  <menu id="kodi.core.main">
    <item library="context-play.py">
      <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32146]</label>
      <visible>[String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Season) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Episode)] | [String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie)]</visible>
    </item>
    <item library="context-open.py">
      <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32147]</label>
      <visible>String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(tvshow.tmdb_id))</visible>
    </item>
    <menu>
      <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32145]</label>
      <item library="context-watchlist.py">
        <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32148]</label>
        <visible>!String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(Container.Info)) + !String.IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(TMDbHelper.TraktIsAuth)) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(tmdb_id)) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)]</visible>
      </item>
      <item library="context-history.py">
        <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32149]</label>
        <visible>!String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(Container.Info)) + !String.IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(TMDbHelper.TraktIsAuth)) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(tmdb_id)) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)]</visible>
      </item>
      <item library="context-collection.py">
        <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32150]</label>
        <visible>!String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(Container.Info)) + !String.IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(TMDbHelper.TraktIsAuth)) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(tmdb_id)) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)]</visible>
      </item>
      <item library="context-library.py">
        <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32151]</label>
        <visible>!String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(Container.Info)) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(tmdb_id)) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,season)]</visible>
      </item>
      <item library="context-library-userlist.py">
        <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32151]</label>
        <visible>!String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(Container.Info)) + String.IsEqual(ListItem.Property(Item.Info),trakt_userlist)</visible>
      </item>
      <item library="context-addtouserlist.py">
        <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32140]</label>
        <visible>!String.IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(TMDbHelper.TraktIsAuth)) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)] + [!String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(tmdb_id)) | !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.DBID)]</visible>
      </item>
      <item library="context-removefromuserlist.py">
        <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32152]</label>
        <visible>!String.IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(TMDbHelper.TraktIsAuth)) + !String.IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(TMDbHelper.TraktUserSlug)) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(Container.User_Slug)) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(Container.List_Slug)) + String.IsEqual(Window(Home).Property(TMDbHelper.TraktUserSlug),ListItem.Property(Container.User_Slug))</visible>
      </item>
      <item library="context-refresh-item.py">
        <label>$ADDON[plugin.video.themoviedb.helper 32153]</label>
        <visible>!String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(Container.Info)) + !String.IsEmpty(ListItem.Property(tmdb_id)) + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.dbtype,tvshow)]</visible>
      </item>
    </menu>
  </menu>
</extension>
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <summary lang="en_GB">TheMovieDb Helper - Now With Trakt Support!</summary>
  <summary lang="es_ES">TheMovieDb Helper - ¡Ahora con soporte para Trakt!</summary>
  <description lang="en_GB">TheMovieDb Helper provides details about movies, tvshows and actors from TMDb. Users can access a variety of lists from TMDb and Trakt.</description>
  <description lang="es_ES">TheMovieDb Helper proporciona detalles sobre películas, programas de televisión y actores de TMDb. Los usuarios pueden acceder a una variedad de listas desde TMDb y Trakt.</description>
  <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Provided by TheMovieDb and Trakt.</disclaimer>
  <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Proporcionado por TheMovieDb y Trakt</disclaimer>
  <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
  <website>https://github.com/jurialmunkey/plugin.video.themoviedb.helper</website>
  <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=345847</forum>
  <assets>
    <icon>icon.png</icon>
    <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
    <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
  </assets>
  <news>Add some additional dbid checking based on title/year combo</news>
</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.unidecode" name="unidecode" version="1.1.1" provider-name="Tomaz Solc (Tomaz.solc@tablix.org)">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.14.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<platform>all</platform>
		<summary lang="en">ASCII transliterations of Unicode text by Sean M. Burke and Tomaz Solc</summary>
		<description lang="en">ASCII transliterations of Unicode text by Sean M. Burke and Tomaz Solc</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Code taken from https://pypi.org/project/Unidecode</disclaimer>
		<license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
		<website>https://pypi.org/project/Unidecode</website>
		<source>https://pypi.org/project/Unidecode</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.urllib3"
       name="urllib3"
       version="1.25.6"
       provider-name="Andrey Petrov">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">HTTP library with thread-safe connection pooling, file post, and more.</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Packed for KODI from https://pypi.org/project/urllib3/</description>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://urllib3.readthedocs.io/en/latest/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/urllib3/urllib3</source>
    <email>freso.dk AT gmail.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.metadatautils"
       name="Metadata and Artwork module"
       version="1.0.27"
       provider-name="marcelveldt, finkleandeinhorn, cartmandos">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8" />
        <import addon="script.module.thetvdb" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="script.module.musicbrainz" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.arrow" version="0.6.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Metadata and artwork from common sources like TMDB, IMDB, TADB and fanart.tv </summary>
        <description>
            The metadata and artwork module for Kodi provides rich metadata, including artwork for
            various metatypes by scraping (and caching) this information from sites like TMDB, musicbrainz and fanart.tv.[CR][CR]
            This product uses the TMDb API but is not endorsed or certified by TMDb
        </description>
        <license>Apache 2.0</license>
        <source>https://github.com/kodi-community-addons/script.module.metadatautils</source>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.allmusic.com"
       name="AllMusic Scraper Library"
        version="3.2.2"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="allmusic.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="en">AllMusic Music Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für AllMusic.com</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">AllMusic musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper AllMusic pour la musique</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">AllMusic zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">AllMusic-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация AllMusic</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för AllMusic.com</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">AllMusic音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.allmusic.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.allmusic.com</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.allmusic.com下载音乐信息</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="visualization.shadertoy" version="1.2.4.1" name="Shadertoy" provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.visualization" version="2.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.player.musicviz" library_linux="visualization.shadertoy.so.1.2.4"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Visualisations from Shadertoy</summary>
    <description lang="en">This music visualization is based on Shadertoy based GPU programs.</description>
    <platform/>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/fanart.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.backgroundoverlays.basic" name="Background Overlays Pack - Basic" version="1.0.0" provider-name="marcelveldt, mgonzales">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false" type="backgroundoverlays" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Pack of images that can be used as background overlay</summary>
		<description lang="en">Pack of images that can be used as background overlay</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.dateutil"
       name="python-dateutil"
       version="2.8.1"
       provider-name="Paul Ganssle, Gustavo Niemeyer">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.six" version="1.12.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Extensions to the standard Python datetime module</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">The dateutil module provides powerful extensions to the standard datetime module, available in Python.</description>
    <license>Apache-2.0, BSD-3-Clause</license>
    <website>https://dateutil.readthedocs.io/en/stable/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/dateutil/dateutil</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.rector.stuff" name="Rector Stuff" version="1.0.3" provider-name="rmrector">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Rector Repository">
		<dir maxversion="18.9.0">
			<info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rmrector/repository.rector.stuff/python2/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rmrector/repository.rector.stuff/python2/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rmrector/repository.rector.stuff/python2/</datadir>
		</dir>
		<dir minversion="19.0.0">
			<info>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rmrector/repository.rector.stuff/python3/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rmrector/repository.rector.stuff/python3/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/rmrector/repository.rector.stuff/python3/</datadir>
		</dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">A little place for my stuff.</summary>
		<description lang="en">I'm Rector, I do stuff, I put it here.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<disclaimer />
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.requests"
       name="requests"
       version="2.22.0"
       provider-name="kennethreitz">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.urllib3" version="1.22"/>
    <import addon="script.module.chardet" version="3.0.4"/>
    <import addon="script.module.idna" version="2.6"/>
    <import addon="script.module.certifi" version="2017.07.27.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Python HTTP for Humans</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Packed for KODI from https://pypi.org/project/requests/</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language></language>
    <license>Apache2</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>http://python-requests.org</website>
    <source>https://github.com/Freso/script.module.requests</source>
    <email>freso.dk AT gmail.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.colorbox" name="colorbox Script" version="2.0.6" provider-name="BADMS">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.module.pil" version="1.1.7"/>
	</requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
	    <summary lang="en_GB">Image manipulator and colour matching tools</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Provides image tools for skinners</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2, June 1991</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/BADMS/script.colorbox</source>
		<email>philipkdick@gmail.com</email>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/fanart.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="vfs.libarchive" version="1.0.7.1" name="Archive support" provider-name="spiff">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.general" version="1.0.3"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.filesystem" version="1.0.2"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.vfs" version="2.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="kodi.vfs" protocols="archive|rar" extensions=".7z|.tar.gz|.tar.bz2|.tar.xz|.zip|.rar|.tgz|.tbz2|.gz|.bz2|.xz|.cbr" files="true" directories="true" filedirectories="true" encodedhostname="true" library_linux="vfs.libarchive.so.1.0.7"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Multi-format archive and compression addon</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">This add-on uses the libarchive library to read a variety of archive and compression formats.

Supported formats are:
7z, tar.gz, tar.bz2, tar.xz, zip, rar, tgz, tbz2, gz, bz2, xz, cbr
</description>
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/vfs.libarchive</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.weathericons.white" name="Weather Icons - White" version="0.0.6" provider-name="Team Kodi">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="true" type="weather" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">White Weather Icons</summary>
		<description lang="en">White Weather Icons</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.thetvdb"
       name="The TVDB API v2"
       version="1.0.27"
       provider-name="marcelveldt">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.arrow" version="0.6.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>TheTVDB API v2 python module for Kodi</summary>
        <description>TheTVDB API v2 python module for Kodi</description>
        <license>Apache 2.0</license>
        <source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.module.thetvdb</source>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="visualization.fishbmc" version="5.1.3.1" name="FishBMC" provider-name="26elf">
  <requires>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.main" version="1.0.14"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.general" version="1.0.3"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.global.gui" version="5.12.0"/>
    <import addon="kodi.binary.instance.visualization" version="2.0.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.player.musicviz" library_linux="visualization.fishbmc.so.5.1.3"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Visualisasie wat Golwe en Wasigheid effek wys</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">إسلوب تخيلي يُظهِر مؤثراتاً بصرية تتضمن موجات ومؤثرات عين السمكة (مؤثرات ضبابية)</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Визуализацията представя вълни и размиващи ефекти</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Vizualizace zobrazující vlny a rozmazané efekty</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Visualisering som viser Waves og Blur effekter</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Visualisierung mit Wellen- und Weichzeichnungs-Effekten</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Οπτικοποίηση προβολής Κυμάτων και Εφέ Θαμπώματος</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Visualisation showing Waves and Blur Effects</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Visualisation showing Waves and Blur Effects</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Visualisation showing Waves and Blur Effects</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Visualización que muestra efectos de ondas y desenfoque</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Visualización que muestra olas y efectos de desenfoque</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Laine- ja uduefektidega visuaal</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Aalto- ja sumennustehosteita näyttävä visualisaatio</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Visualisation montrant des vagues et des effets de flou</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Visualisation à effet de vague et flou</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Unha visualización con Ondas e efectos de Desenfoque</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">חיזוי מציג אפקטי גלים וטשטוש</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Vizualizacija prikazuje valove i zamućene efekte</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">A vizualizáció Hullámokat és Elmosás Effekteket mutat.</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Visualisasi menunjukkan efek gelombang dan efek kabur.</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Visualizzazione mostrando Onde e Sfumature</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Vizualizācija, rādot viļņus un izpludināšanas efektu</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Visualisatie waarbij Golven en Blur effecten worden getoond </summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Wizualizacja prezentuje efekty fali i rozmycia</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Uma visualização com Ondas e Efeitos de Desfocagem</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Visualização mostrando Ondas e Efeitos Borrados</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Vizualizácia zobrazujúca vlnky a efekty rozmazania</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Vizualizacija prikazuje valovanje in učinke zamegljenosti</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Visualisering bestående av vågor- och blur-effekter</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">அலைகள் மற்றும் தெளிவின்மை விளைவுகள் காண்பிக்கும் காட்சி அமைப்பு</summary>
    <summary lang="tg_tj">Таҷассум бо шамоиши мавҷҳо ва таъсирҳои хирагӣ</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">呈现波浪和模糊效果的可视化效果</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">fishBMC is gebasseer op fische, 'n onafhanklike klank visulasasie program. Die basiese prinsiep is: teken die golflente en smeer die tekening langs Vooraf gedefinieerde vektore. fische sluit ook gevorderde tempo ondekking in, wat 'n besondere visuele ervaring verseker.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">fishBMC е създадена въз основа на fische - самостоятелен инструмент за визуализиране на звук. Основния принцип е изчертаване на вълнова функция и размиване по предварително определени вектори. В допълнение fische съдържа и разширена функция за засичане на ритъма, което би трябвало да гарантира великолепно визуално изживяване.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">fishBMX er baseret på fische, et standard visualiserings værktøj. Det basale princip er: tegn waveformen og tvær tegning langs de prædefinerede vektorer. fische inkluderer også avanceret beat registrering, som garanterer en god visuel oplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">fishBMC basiert auf fische, einem eigenständigen Ton-Visualisierungs-Programm. Das Grundprinzip ist: zeichne das Wellen-Spektrum und verwische die Zeichnung entlang festgelegter Vektoren. fische verfügt jedoch auch über eine fortgeschrittene Rhytmus-Erkennung, die ein großartiges visuelles Erlebnis garantiert.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Το fishBMC είναι βασισμένο στο fische, ένα ξεχωριστό εργαλείο ηχητικών οπτικοποιήσεων. Η βασική του αρχή είναι: σχεδίαση μιας κυματομορφής και χρωματισμός της εικόνας κατά μήκος προκαθορισμένων διανυσμάτων. Παρ'όλα αυτά, το fische περιλαμβάνει και ανεπτυγμένες μεθόδους εντοπισμού παλμών, γεγονός που εγγυάται μια εκπληκτική οπτική εμπειρία.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualisation tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualisation tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualisation tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">fishBMC está basado en fische, una herramienta de visualización de sonido. El principio básico es: dibujar la forma de onda y extender a lo largo de vectores predefinidos. Sin embargo, fische también incluye una avanzada detección de ritmos, lo cual garantiza una gran experiencia visual. </description>
    <description lang="es_MX">fishBMC se basa en fische, una herramienta independiente de visualización de sonido. El principio principal es: dibujar la forma de onda y esfumar el dibujo en conjunto a vectores predefinidos. No obstante, fische también incorpora una detección avanzada de compás, lo que garantiza una gran experiencia visual.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">fishBMC baseerub fische visualiseerimistööriistal. Põhiprintsiibiks on: joonista laine ja määri see ettenähtud suundades laiali. fische sisaldab lisaks veel edasijõudnud rütmituvastajat, garanteerides nii vaatajale suurepärase elamuse. </description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">fishBMC est basé sur fische, un outil de visualisation sonore. Le principe de base est : dessiner des ondes et déplacer le tracé sur les vecteurs prédéfinit. Cependant fische incorpore aussi un système de détection des battements, ce qui garantie une grande expérience visuelle.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">fishBMX est basé sur fische, un outil de visualisation audio autonome. Le principe de base est : dessiner la forme de l'onde et altère le dessin suivant des vecteurs prédéfinis. Cependant fische incorpore aussi une détection améliorée du tempo, ce qui garantie une expérience visuelle de qualité</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">fishBMC está baseado en fische, unha ferramenta autónoma de visualización de sons. O principio básico é: debuxar as formas de onda e pintalas ao longo dos vectores predefinidos. E posíbel que fische tamén incorpore detección avanzada de golpes, que realmente garante unha grande experiencia visual.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">fishBMC מבוסס על fische, כלי לחיזוי סאונד. העקרון הבסיסי הוא: צייר צורת גל ומרח את הציור לאורך הוקטורים המוגדרים מראש. אבל fische הוא גם שילוב מקצועי של זיהוי מקצבים, אשר מעניק חווית חיזוי נהדרת.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">fishBMC je temeljen na fische, samostalnom alatu zvučne vizualizacije. Osnovno načelo je: iscrtati valni oblik i razmazati crtež unaprijed određenim vektorima. Međutim fische isto uključuje napredno otkrivanje taktova, koje uistinu jamči sjajno vizualno iskustvo.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">fishBMC a fische-n alapul, egy önálló hangvizualizációs eszköz. A fő célkitűzése: a hanghullám kirajzolása és előre megadott vektorok szerinti módosítása. Viszont a fische szintén alkalmaz egy haladó ütemérzékelőt, ami tényleg garantálja a nagyszerű vizuális élményt.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">fishBMC didasarkan fische, alat visualisasi suara yang berdiri sendiri. Prinsip dasarnya adalah mengambar gelombang dan mengaburkannya sepanjang vektor yang telah ditentukan. Namun fische juga mengikutsertakan deteksi ketukan yang canggih, yang akan menjamin pengalaman visual yang hebat.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">fishBMC si basa su fische, uno strumento di visualizzazione del suono standalone. Il principio di base è: disegnare la forma d'onda e spalmare il disegno lungo i vettori predefiniti. Tuttavia fische incorpora anche il rilevamento di battito avanzato, che garantisce un'ottima esperienza visiva.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">fishBMC is based on fische, a standalone sound visualisation tool. The basic principle is: draw the waveform and smear the drawing along predefined vectors. However fische also incorporates advanced beat detection, which really guarantees a great visual experience.</description>
    <description lang="lv_LV">fishBMC pamatā ir savrups skaņas vizualizācijas rīks "fische". Pamatdoma ir zīmēt skaņas viļņus un iztriept tos pa iepriekš noteiktiem vektoriem. Tomēr fische iekļauta arī papildus ritma noteikšanas metode, kas patiešām garantē lielisku vizuālo baudījumu.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">FishBMC is gebaseerd op fische, een zelfstandige geluidsvisualisatie tool. Het basis principe is: Teken de golfvorm en veeg de tekening rondom voor ingestelde richting. Echter fische brengt eveneens geavanceerde beat detectie, wat echt een grote visuele beleving garandeerd.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">fishBMC bazuje na fische, samodzielne narzędzie do wizualizacji muzyki. Podstawową zasadą jest generowanie wykresu fali i rozmazywanie go wzdłuż zdefiniowanych wektorów. Ponadto fische zawiera również zaawansowaną detekcję rytmu, co gwarantuje wspaniałe wrażenia wizualne.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">O fishBMC é baseado no fische, uma ferramenta autónoma de visualização de sons. O princípio básico é desenhar a onda e deformar o desenho através de vectores pré-definidos. No entanto, o fische também incorpora detecção avançada de ritmos, garantindo uma excelente experiência visual.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">fishBMC é baseado no fische, uma ferramenta de visualização de som independente. O princípio básico é: desenhar a forma de onda e esmaecer o desenho ao longo de vetores pré-definidos. Entretanto fische também incorpora detecção avançada de batidas, o que realmente garante uma grande experiência visual.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">fishBMC je založený na fische, samostatnom nástroji na vizualizáciu. Základným princípom je: nakresliť priebeh signálu a rozmazať kresbu pozdĺž predefinovaných vektorov. Navyše fische obsahuje aj pokročilú detekciu rytmu, čo garantuje skutočný vizuálny zážitok.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">fishBMC temelji na fischeu, samostojnem zvočno vizualizacijskem orodju. Osnovno načelo je: nariši valovni način in ga razmaži vzdolž vnaprej določenih vektorjev. Fische prav tako vključuje tudi napredno zaznavanje ritma, ki resnično zagotavlja odlično vizualno izkušnjo.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">fishBMC är baserat på fische, ett fristående verktyg för ljudvisualisering. Den grundläggande principen är: rita en vågform och smeta ut den längs förbestämda vektorer. fische inkluderar även avancerad rytmdetektion, vilket verkligen garanterar en härlig visuell upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">fische என்பது ஒரு முழுமையான ஒலி காட்சிப்படுத்தல் கருவி இதை சார்ந்ததாகும் fishBMC என்பது. அடிப்படை கொள்கை ஆனது: அலைவடிவம் வரையவும் மற்றும் முன்வடிவகிக்கபட்ட வெக்டார்கள் சேர்த்து வரையப்படும். ஆனால் fische ஆனது மேலும் மேம்பட்ட துடிப்பு கண்டறிதல் திறனை உள்ளடக்கியது, உண்மையில் ஒரு காட்சி அனுபவத்தை உறுதி செய்யும்.</description>
    <description lang="tg_tj">fishBMC дар асоси fische, абзори алоҳида барои таҷассуми садо, амал мекунад. Қоидаи асосӣ: кашидани векторҳои мавҷшакл ва бетартиб. Инчунин fische муайянкунии зарбазании иловагии дарунсохтро таъмин менамояд, ки дар ҳақиқат таҷассуми аҷибро замонат медиҳад.</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">fishBMC 基于一个独立的声音可视化工具 fische。基本原理是：绘制波型并按预定的顶点涂抹。fische 还采用了先进的节拍检测，从而真正保证了绝佳的视觉体验。</description>
    <disclaimer lang="af_ZA">As dit iets breek, bly die stukke joune.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ar_SA">إذا سبب هذا تحطم أى شيئ، فستبقي القطع ملكك!</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="bg_BG">Ако "счупи" нещо - парчетата остават за Вас!</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da_DK">Hvis dette ødelægger noget, er stykkerne dine.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Für eventuelle Schäden wird keine Haftung übernommen.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el_GR">Αν σπάσει τίποτα, θα σας μείνουν τα κομμάτια.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">If this breaks anything, the pieces remain yours.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_AU">If this breaks anything, the pieces remain yours.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">If this breaks anything, the pieces remain yours.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Si esto rompe alguna cosa, te puedes quedar con los trozos.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es_MX">Si esto rompe algo, las piezas siguen siento tuyas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="et_EE">kui see midagi lõhub, siis võid tükid endale jätta</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Si cela casse quelque chose, les pièces restent les vôtres.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Si ça brise, vous gardez les morceaux.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="gl_ES">Se isto estraga algunha cousa, pode quedar cas pezas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hr_HR">Ako ovo slomi nešto, komadići ostaju vama.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu_HU">Ha ez összetör valamit attól a darabok még a tieid maradnak.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="id_ID">Kalau ini merusakkan suatu, pecahannya tetap menjadi milik anda.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it_IT">se si rompe qualcosa, i cocci sono vostri.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt_LT">Jei tai sugenda nieko, gabaliukai lieka tavo.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lv_LV">Ja tas kaut ko saplēš, lauskas paliek tev.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Gebruik maken van deze visualisatie is op eigen risico.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl_PL">Jeśli to rozbije cokolwiek, kawałki pozostaną Twoje.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_PT">Se isto quebrar alguma coisa, pode ficar com as peças.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">se isto quebrar algo, as peças serão suas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk_SK">Ak toto niečo rozbije, kúsky vám ostanú.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sl_SI">V primeru, da to karkoli zlomi, koščki ostanejo vaši.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv_SE">Om detta skulle förstöra något så kan du behålla resterna.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ta_IN">எதையாவது இது உடைக்குமேயானால், உடைந்த துகல்கள் உங்களுடையது.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="tg_tj">Агар ин чизеро вайрон кунад, шумо қисмҳоро мегиред.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">用者责任自负。</disclaimer>
    <platform/>
    <license>GPL-2.0</license>
    <source>https://github.com/xbmc/visualization.fishbmc</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.service" name="Skin Helper Service" version="1.1.24" provider-name="marcelveldt">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.13.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.metadatautils" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.cherrypy" version="11.0.0"/>
	</requires>

    <extension point="kodi.context.item">
        <menu id="kodi.core.main">
            <item library="resources\lib\context_animatedart.py">
              <label>32024</label>
              <visible>!IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(SkinHelper.EnableAnimatedPosters)) + Container.Content(movies)</visible>
            </item>
            <item library="resources\lib\context_pvr.py">
                <label>32023</label>
                <description>PVR artwork Configuration</description>
                <visible>
                    !IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(SkinHelper.EnablePvrThumbs)) +
                    [Window.IsActive(MyPVRChannels.xml) |
                    Window.IsActive(MyPVRGuide.xml) | Window.IsActive(MyPVRRecordings.xml) |
                    Window.IsActive(MyPVRTimers.xml) | Window.IsActive(MyPVRSearch.xml)]
                </visible>
            </item>
            <item library="resources\lib\context_music.py">
                <label>32023</label>
                <description>Music artwork Configuration</description>
                <visible>
                    !IsEmpty(Window(Home).Property(SkinHelper.EnableMusicArt)) +
                    [Container.Content(albums) | Container.Content(artists) | Container.Content(songs)]
                </visible>
            </item>
        </menu>
	</extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
    </extension>
	<extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="login" />

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Helper service for Kodi skins</summary>
        <description>Helper service for Kodi skins</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.skin.helper.service</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.skinbackup" name="Skin Helper Service Skin Backup" version="1.0.19" provider-name="marcelveldt">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.13.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
	</requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py" />
	<extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="login" />

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Helper service for Kodi skins</summary>
        <description>Helper service for Kodi skins</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<source>https://github.com/marcelveldt/script.skin.helper.skinbackup</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.skinshortcuts" name="Skin Shortcuts" version="1.0.19" provider-name="BigNoid,marcelveldt">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.20.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.unidecode" version="0.4.14"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<news>Template improvements and bug fixes</news>
		<description lang="bg">Добавка за облици, която осигурява просто управление и списък с потребителски преки пътища (изисква поддръжка от облика)</description>
		<description lang="de">Add-on für Skins für einfache Bearbeitung und Auflistung von benutzerdefinierten Verknüpfungen (erfordert Skin-Unterstützung)</description>
		<description lang="el">Πρόσθετο για κελύφη, το οποίο παρέχει έναν απλό τρόπο διαχείρισης και κατηγοριοποίησης των συντομεύσεων του χρήστη (πρέπει να υποστηρίζεται από το κέλυφος)</description>
		<description lang="en">Add-on for skins to provide simple managing and listing of user shortcuts (requires skin support)</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">Add-on for skins to provide simple managing and listing of user shortcuts (requires skin support)</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Add-on for skins to provide simple managing and listing of user shortcuts (requires skin support)</description>
		<description lang="es">Complemento para las pieles para proporcionar una gestión sencilla y lista de atajos de usuario (requiere que la piel lo soporte)</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">Addiciel pour habillages qui fournit une gestion simple et un listage des raccourcis utilisateurs (exige la prise en charge de l'habillage)</description>
		<description lang="gl">Complemento que fornece aos temas dunha xestión sinxela dos atallos dos usuarios (require soporte do tema)</description>
		<description lang="hr">Dodatak za presvlake koja omogućava jednostavno upravljanje i prikaz korisnikovih prečaca (zahtijeva podršku presvlake) </description>
		<description lang="hu">Felszín kiegészítő amely könnyen kezelhetővé és listázhatóvá teszi a felhasználói parancsikonokat (Felszín támogatás szükséges)</description>
		<description lang="is">Viðbót fyrir viðmót til að halda utan um flýtivísa og fá yfirlit yfir þá (þarfnast stuðnings frá viðmóti)</description>
		<description lang="it">Add-on per gli skin per consentire un facile gestione ed elenco delle scorciatoie utente (richiede che lo skin lo supporti)</description>
		<description lang="lt">Priedas teminėms išvaizdoms, kad jos turėtų galimybę paprastai tvarkyti ir atvaizduoti vartotojo  sukurtas nuorodas (reikalingas teminės išvaizdos palaikymas)</description>
		<description lang="nl">Add-on voor skins om te voorzien in het eenvoudig beheren en sorteren van gebruikers snelkoppelingen (vereist skin ondersteuning)</description>
		<description lang="no">Tillegg for enkel administrering og opplisting av bruker-snarveier i tema (krever støtte i tema)</description>
		<description lang="pl">Wtyczka dla skór, która zapewnia proste zarządzanie i tworzenie list skrótów użytkownika (wymaga wsparcia skóry)</description>
		<description lang="pt">Um add-on que permite que os temas tenham recursos simples para gerir e listar atalhos de utilizadores (é necessário suporte do tema)</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">Add-on para que as skins possam prover gerenciamento de lista de atalhos para o menu principal (requer suporte da skin)</description>
		<description lang="ru">Дополнение для обложек, предоставляющее простой способ управления и список пользовательских ярлыков (требуется поддержка обложкой)</description>
		<description lang="sv">Skinntillägg som tillhandahåller enkel hantering och översikt av användargenvägar (om skinnet stöder det)</description>
		<description lang="zh">插件为皮肤提供了简单的管理和用户连接方式列表 (需要皮肤支持)</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU General Public License, v2</license>
		<forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=178294</forum>
		<website></website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/BigNoid/script.skinshortcuts</source>
	<assets>
		<icon>icon.png</icon>
		<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
	</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.amber" version="3.2.23" name="Amber" provider-name="Jester, Joethepartylion, Pecinko, bsoriano">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.14.0"/>
        <import addon="script.favourites" version="7.1.1"/>
        <import addon="resource.uisounds.amber" version="1.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.skin.helper.widgets" version="1.0.22"/>
        <import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="1.0.17"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
        <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="cs_CZ">Nic zbytečného, jenom vaše media a snadné ovládání</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Keine Bloatware, nur Ihre Medien mit einer leicht zu navigierenden Oberfläche</summary>
        <summary lang="en_AU">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Sin chorradas, solo su contenido con una interfaz fácil de navegar</summary>
        <summary lang="fi_FI">Ei sisällä turhia lisäominaisuuksia. Yksinkertainen käyttöliittymä mediakirjastollesi.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Pas d’inflagiciel, juste vos médias avec une interface facile à parcourir</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Pas d'usine à gaz, juste les médias avec une interface épurée</summary>
        <summary lang="he_IL">אין כלים נוספים, רק התקשורת שלך עם ממשק קל לניווט</summary>
        <summary lang="hu_HU">Semmi pazarlás, csak a médiáid, könnyen navigálható felülettel</summary>
        <summary lang="is_IS">Alls ekki óþarfa prjál, heldur bara margmiðlunarefnið þitt með einföldu viðmóti</summary>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Skin leggera, i tuoi media con un'interfaccia semplice in cui navigare</summary>
        <summary lang="ko_KR">블로트웨어가 아닙니다. 쉬운 탐색 인터페이스를 가진 사용자의 미디어 자체입니다.</summary>
        <summary lang="lt_LT">Nieko nereikalingo, tik jūsų media įrašai ir lengvai valdoma vartotojo sąsaja</summary>
        <summary lang="ms_MY">Tiada perisian palsu, hanya media anda dengan antaramuka yang mudah dinavigasi</summary>
        <summary lang="nb_NO">Ingen tunge og unødvendige funksjoner, bare dine media og ett lettvint grensesnitt</summary>
        <summary lang="nl_NL">Geen bloatware, alleen jouw media in een makkelijk te navigeren omgeving</summary>
        <summary lang="pl_PL">Bez zbędnych funkcji, tylko Twoje media z intuicyjnym interfejsem</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Sem bloatware, apenas sua mídia com uma interface fácil de navegar</summary>
        <summary lang="sl_SI">Brez napihnjenega programja, zgolj vaši mediji z vmesnikom, enostavnim za krmarjenje.</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">没有大的软件，只有你的媒体和易于浏览的界面</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_TW">只有您的影音和簡單的界面</summary>
        <description lang="ar_SA">بلا برمجيات متضخمة، فقط وسائط </description>
        <description lang="cs_CZ">Nic zbytečného, jenom vaše media a snadné ovládání[CR] Použité některé textury z projektů Mediastream a Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">Keine Bloatware, nur Ihre Medien mit einer einfach zu navigierenden Oberfläche.[CR]Benutzt Texturen aus den Mediastream und Aeon skins.</description>
        <description lang="en_AU">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface.[CR]Uses some textures from Mediastream and Aeon skins.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface.[CR]Uses some textures from Mediastream and Aeon skins.</description>
        <description lang="en_NZ">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface.[CR]Uses some textures from Mediastream and Aeon skins.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">No bloatware, just your media with an easy to navigate interface.[CR]Uses some textures from Mediastream and Aeon skins.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Sin chorradas, sólo su contenido con una interfaz fácil de navegar.[CR]Utiliza algunas texturas de los skins Mediastream y Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="fi_FI">Ei sisällä turhia lisäominaisuuksia. Yksinkertainen käyttöliittymä mediakirjastollesi.[CR]Käyttää joitakin kuvatiedostoja Mediastream- ja Aeon-ulkoasuista.</description>
        <description lang="fr_CA">Pas d’inflagiciel, juste vos médias avec une interface facile à parcourir.[CR]Utilise des textures des habillages Mediastream et Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">Pas d'utilisation excessive des ressources, juste vos médias avec une interface facile à utiliser.[CR]Utilise quelques textures provenant des habillages Mediastream et Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="he_IL">מעטפת קלילה וללא רכיבים מיותרים, מאפשרת הצגת המדיה עם ממשק משתמש פשוט לניווט.[CR]משתמשת במאפייני עיצוב מסוימים מהמעטפות Mediastream ו-Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="hu_HU">Semmi pazarlás, csak a médiáid, könnyen navigálható felülettel.[CR]Néhány textúra a Mediastream és Aeon felszínből származik.</description>
        <description lang="is_IS">Alls ekki óþarfa prjál, heldur bara margmiðlunarefnið þitt með einföldu viðmóti.[CR]Notar ýmsar áferðir úr Mediastream og Aeon skinnunum.</description>
        <description lang="it_IT">Skin leggera, i tuoi media con un'interfaccia semplice in cui navigare.[CR]Usa alcuni elementi grafici delle skin Mediastream e Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="ko_KR">블로트웨어가 아닌 그냥 쉬운 탐색 인터페이스를 가진 사용자의 미디어입니다.[CR]Mediastream 과 Aeon 스킨의 텍스처를 사용하였습니다.</description>
        <description lang="lt_LT">Nieko nereikalingo, tik jūsų media įrašai ir lengvai valdoma vartotojo sąsaja. [CR] Naudoja kai kurias tekstūras iš Mediastream ir Aeon temų.</description>
        <description lang="ms_MY">Bukan perisian palsu, hanya media anda dengan antaramuka yang mudah dinavigasi.[CR]Gunakan beberapa tekstur dari kulit Mediastream dan Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="nb_NO">Ingen tunge og unødvendige funksjoner, bare dine media og ett lettvint grensesnitt.[CR]Noen teksturer er hentet fra Mediastream og Aeon -draktene.</description>
        <description lang="nl_NL">Geen bloatware. alleen jouw media met een makkelijk te navigeren interface.[CR]Gebruikt sommige texturen van de Mediastream- en Aeonontwerpen.</description>
        <description lang="pl_PL">Bez bezużytecznych funkcji, tylko Twoje media z łatwym w nawigacji interfejsem.[CR] Wykorzystuje niektóre tekstury skóry Mediastream i Aeon</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Sem excessos, apenas a sua mídia com uma interface fácil de navegar. [CR]Utiliza algumas texturas das skins Mediastream e Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="pt_PT">Um tema sem excessos que apenas mostra a sua média com uma interface de navegação simples.[CR]Utiliza algumas texturas dos temas Mediastream e Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="ru_RU">Никаких вирусов, только ваши медиа файлы в простом интерфейсе.[CR]Использует некоторые текстуры из тем Mediastream и Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="sl_SI">Brez nepotrebnega, le vaše medijske datoteke z enostavnim vmesnikom.[CR]Uporablja nekatere teksture iz tem Mediastream in Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="sv_SE">Inget överflödigt, bara dina media med enkelt navigeringsinterface.[CR]Använder texturer från skalen Mediastream och Aeon.</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">没有花里胡哨的东西，只是你的媒体和易于浏览的界面。[CR]使用了一些来自 Mediastream 和 Aeon 皮肤的纹理材料.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, June 2007</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=203</forum>
        <source>https://github.com/bartolomesoriano/skin.amber</source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot04.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot05.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot06.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot07.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot08.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot09.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot10.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <news>3.2.23 (12-10-2019)
        - Remove all Matrix code from Leia version
        3.2.22 (09-10-2019)
        - Fixes to blur settings
        - Changes to fanart view
        - Make TV Show clickable for episodes in video info
        3.2.21 (07-10-2019)
        - Fixes for latest tmdb helper version
        3.2.20 (06-10-2019)
        - Many changes! (please see changelog.txt)
        3.2.9 (24-07-2019)
     - Make home background title clickable. Opens custom search.
        3.2.8 (20-07-2019)
     - Fix missing updates to the Amber repo
     - Fix sets info in Matrix when Extendedinfo enabled
        3.2.7 (19-07-2019)
     - Add missing skin playlists default shelves
     - Misc. fixes
        3.2.6 (19-07-2019)
     - Show Ratings as percent
     - Be able to expand addon description in info
        3.2.5 (17-07-2019)
     - Add missing skinning changes for Kodi Matrix
        3.2.4 (16-07-2019)
     - Update French translation</news>
    </extension>
</addon>

	<addon id="script.skin.helper.widgets" name="Skin Helper Service Widgets" version="1.1.2" provider-name="marcelveldt,patrick-klein,cartman.dos">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
		<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.metadatautils" version="1.0.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.simplecache" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>

	<extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="plugin.py">
        <provides>video audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="login" />

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Ready to use widgets for all kind of media types</summary>
        <description></description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v2.0</license>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=235676</forum>
		<website></website>
		<source>https://github.com/cartmandos/script.skin.helper.widgets</source>
		<news>
			[B]v1.1.1[/B][CR]A lot of new widgets to choose from![CR]Bug fixes and other improvements[CR]Follow the forum thread about the latest news.[CR]https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=334820
		</news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.chardet"
       name="chardet"
       version="3.0.4"
       provider-name="Dan Blanchard">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Universal encoding detector</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Packed for Kodi from https://github.com/chardet/chardet</description>
    <license>LGPL</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language></language>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>https://chardet.readthedocs.io/en/latest/</website>
    <source>https://github.com/beenje/script.module.chardet</source>
    <email>beenje AT gmail.com</email>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.myconnpy"
       name="MySQL Connector/Python"
       version="1.1.7"
       provider-name="MySQL">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">MySQL Connector/Python</summary>
        <description lang="en">MySQL Connector/Python is implementing the MySQL Client/Server protocol completely in Python. This means you don't have to compile anything or MySQL (client library) doesn't even have to be installed on the machine.</description>
        <license>GPLv2</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <website>http://dev.mysql.com/doc/connector-python/en/index.html</website>
        <source>http://dev.mysql.com/downloads/connector/python/</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com"
       name="TheAudioDb Scraper Library"
       version="2.0.3"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="tadb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на музикална инф. от TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en">TheAudioDb Music Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Musik-Scraper für TheAudioDb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de música de TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">TheAudioDb musiikkitietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper TheAudioDb pour la musique</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">TheAudioDb zenei adat leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">TheAudioDb-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper muzyki TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de música TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog de muzică TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Музыкальная Информация TheAudioDb</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för TheAudioDb.org</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">TheAudioDb音乐刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Извлича инф. за музикални файлове от www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Music information from www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloade Musik Informationen von www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga información musical de www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa musiikkitietoja osoitteesta www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharger les infos musicales depuis www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Zene információk letöltése a www.theaudiodb.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Muziekinformatie ophalen van www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o muzyce z www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de música de www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați informații muzică de pe www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать информацию о Музыке с www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner musikinformation från www.theaudiodb.com</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.theaudiodb.com下载音乐信息</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.common.plugin.cache" name="Common plugin cache" provider-name="anxdpanic, TheCollective" version="2.6.1">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.24.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/entry_point.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="resources/lib/storage_server/"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <news>
[fix] shutdown taking longer than 5 seconds
[fix] ignore encoding issues for socket data
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <summary lang="en_GB">A common caching API for Kodi add-ons.</summary>
        <license>GPL-3.0-only</license>
        <source>https://github.com/anxdpanic/script.common.plugin.cache</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.covenant" name="[B][COLOR blue]Covenant[/COLOR] Repository[/B]" version="0.1" provider-name="Covenant">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Covenant Repo">

		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/covenant01/plugins/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/covenant01/plugins/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/covenant01/plugins/master</datadir>
		</dir>

		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>

		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openmeta/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openmeta/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openmeta/master/zips/</datadir>
		</dir>

		<dir>
			<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml</info>
			<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
			<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/</datadir>
	        </dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">[B][COLOR blue]Covenant[/COLOR][/B] We do not host any of the contents streamed</summary>
		<description lang="en">[B][COLOR blue]Covenant[/COLOR][/B] - This addon does not form part of the Kodi Media Centre. Please do not seek assistance with this addon from any of the Official Kodi Support Channels.The author does not host any of the content in this addon and takes no responsibility for content found.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">The author is not responsible for the use of this addon. The author is not responsible for the content found using this addon. The author does not host or own any content found within this addon. The author is in no way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation. This is a Non-profit resource, organized solely for educational purposes which is protected under the Fair-Use doctrine of the Copyright Act, Specifically section 107, which does promote freedom of expression, by permitting the unlicensed use of copyright-protected works</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
		</assets>
		<news></news>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.thecrew.metadata" version="0.0.5" name="[COLOR orchid]THE CREW METADATA[/COLOR]" provider-name="The Crew">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">The Crew is a team of individuals that does what it can to provide others, you the best in entertainment.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Many come, Many go. The true and dedicated are here.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon do not host any of the content which is found and have no affiliation with any of the content providers. This addon simply searches websites for content. Use at your own risk!</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.imdb.com"
       name="IMDB Scraper Library"
       version="3.1.6"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="imdb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от IMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="en">IMDB Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">IMDB elokuvatietojen lataaja</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">IMDB leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="kr">IMDB 스크래퍼 라이브러리</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">IMDB Scraper Bibliotheek</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper IMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de filmes IMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapa för IMDB</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация за филми от www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="en">Download Movie information from www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa elokuvatietoja osoitteesta www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="hu">Film információk letöltése a www.imdb.com webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="kr">www.imdb.com 에서 영화 정보 다운로드</description>
    <description lang="nl">Download film informatie van www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj informacje o filmach z www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de www.imdb.com</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner filminformation från www.imdb.com</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.image.resource.select" name="Image Resource Select Addon" version="2.0.4" provider-name="ronie">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="default.py"/>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Image resource selection addon</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">Script for skinners to let users select an image resource addon.</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=239558</forum>
		<source>https://gitlab.com/ronie/script.image.resource.select</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.album.universal"
       name="Universal Album Scraper"
       version="3.1.3"
       provider-name="Olympia, Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="2.1.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.8.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.albums"
             language="en"
             library="albumuniversal.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Universele Skraper vir Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="ast">Scraper universal pa álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Универсален източник за информация за албуми</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Arreplegador universal per àlbums</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro alba</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Crafwr Albymau Cyffredinol</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Universel Scraper til Albummer</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Universeller Scraper für Alben</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Universal Scraper Άλμπουμ</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Scraper universal para álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper Universal para Albumes</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal para Álbumes</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Universaalne albumite kraabits</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Universaali tiedonhakija albumitiedoille</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Scraper universel pour les Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur universel pour les albums</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Scraper Universal para Álbums</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">סקרייפר אוניברסלי עבור אלבומים</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Univerzalni sakupljač informacija albuma</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Univerzális album leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Pengais Universal Album</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Universal Scraper fyrir Hljómplötur</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Ricercatore Universale per Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">汎用アルバムスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Universal Scraper for Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Universalus albumų skreperis</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Albumu universālais skrāpis</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Универзален превземач за Албуми</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Pengikis Universel untuk Album</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Universele Scraper voor Albums</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Universalskraper for album</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Uniwersalny ekstraktor informacji o albumach muzycznych</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Colector universal para álbuns</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Álbuns</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO"> Scraper universal pentru albume</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Универсальный скрапер для альбомов</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre albumy</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Univerzalni ponudnik informacij o albumih</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Universiell albumskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">ஆல்பங்களின் ஒட்டு மொத்தமான சுரண்டி</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Albümler için Evrensel Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Універсальний здирач для альбомів</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Trình lấy dữ liệu album từ nhiều nguồn</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">通用音乐专辑信息刮削器</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">通用音樂專輯訊息搜刮器</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Hierdie skraper kollekteer inligting vanaf die volgende ondersteunde werwe: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com en amazon.de, terwyl kunswerke gegryp word vanaf: fanart.tv, last.fm en allmusic.com. Dit kan veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifieke inligting wil hê.&#10;&#10;Die aanvaklike soektog word altyd op MusicBrainz gedoen. Ingeval skakels van allmusic en/of amazon.de nie bygevoeg is op die MusicBrainz werf, kan velde vanaf allmusic.com en/of amazon.de nie gaan haal word nie (egter baie maklik om daardie ontbrekende skakels by te voeg).</description>
    <description lang="ast">Esti scraper recueye información de les siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mentanto obtién les imáxenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quier obtener la información pa cada campu. ⏎ ⏎ La gueta inicial faise siempre en MusicBrainz. En casu de que los enllaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de nun tean amestaos na web de MusicBrainz, nun van poder obtenese los campos d'información d' estos dos sitios (magar que ye mui fácil amestar esos enllaces que falten)</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com и amazon.de. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, last.fm и allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не са налични препратки към allmusic и/или amazon.de на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com и/или amazon.de става невъзможно (добавянето им е много лесно).</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com i amazon.de, alhora que agafa art de: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Es pot configurar camp a camp des de quin lloc voleu aquella informació específica. &#10;&#10;La cerca inicial es realitza sempre a MusicBrainz. En el cas que els enllaços d'allmusic i amazon.de no s'afegeixin al lloc MusicBrainz els camps d'allmusic i amazon.de i/o amazon.com no es poden obtenir (tot i que són fàcils d'afegir aquests enllaços restants).</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Tento zdroj získává data z následujících podporovaných stránek: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možno podrobně nastavit, které informace si přejete získat ze kterých stránek.&#10;&#10;Prvotní vyhledání je vžy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že odkaz pro allmusic a nebo amazon.de není přidaný na stránku MusicBrainz, není možné údaje z allmusic.com a amazon.de stáhnout (avšak je velmi snadné tyto chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mae'r crafwr yn casglu gwybodaeth o'r gwefannau canlynol:  MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ac amazon.de, tra'n cipio gwaith celf o: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. Mae modd ei osod fesul maes i ddewis pa wefan i gasglu gwybodaeth benodol.&#10;&#10;Bydd y chwilio cychwynnol yn cael ei wneud ar MusicBrainz. Rhag ofn nad yw dolen allmusic wedi ei osod ar wefan MusicBrainz nid oes modd estyn meysydd o allmusic.com (mae'n hawdd gosod y dolenni coll hynny)</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Det kan vælges felt for felt, hvilke sider du ønsker, at få den pågældende information fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic og/eller amazon.de linkene er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Dieser Scaper sammelt Informationen von den folgenden, unterstützten Seiten: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, Allmusic.com und Amazon.de. Es werden dabei Grafiken von den folgenden Seiten geladen: Fanart.tv, Last.fm und Allmusic.com. Von welcher Seite die Informationen geladen werden, kann einzeln konfiguriert werden.⏎ &#10;⏎&#10;Die initialie Suche wird immer über MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollten keine Allmusic- und/oder Amazon.de-Links auf der MusicBrainz-Seite gesetzt worden sein, können Felder von Allmusic.com und/oder Amazon.de nicht geladen werden (fehlende Links können jedoch sehr einfach hinzugefügt werden).</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες υποστηριζόμενες ιστοσελίδες: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com και amazon.de, ενώ λαμβάνει εικόνες από τα: fanart.tv, last.fm και allmusic.com. Μπορεί να οριστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο αναλόγως των πληροφοριών που επιθυμείτε από την εκάστοτε ιστοσελίδα.&#10;&#10;Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο MusicBrainz. Σε περίπτωση που δεν έχουν προστεθεί σύνδεσμοι για το allmusic ή/και το amazon.de στο MusicBrainz, δε θα μπορούν να ληφθούν πεδία από το allmusic.com ή/και το amazon.de (ωστόσο είναι πολύ εύκολο να προστεθούν αυτοί οι ελλιπείς σύνδεσμοι).</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información para cada campo. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de estos dos sitios (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información para cada campo. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic y/o amazon.de no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de estos dos sitios (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com y amazon.de, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic y/o amazon.de no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com y/o amazon.de no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">See kraabits kogub infot järgmistelt lehtedelt: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ja amazon.de, pilte: fanart.tv, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Saad välja kaupa määrata, milliselt lehelt mis infot soovid.&#10;&#10;Esmane otsing tehakse alati saidilt MusicBrainz. Kui MusicBrainz lehele pole allmusic ja/või amazon.de linke lisatud, siis neilt lehtedelt sisu hankida ei saa (puuduvaid linke saad ise lihtsalt lisada).</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Tämä tiedonhakija käyttää tietolähteinään seuraavia sivustoja:MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ja amazon.de. Kuvat ja grafiikat haetaan seuraavilta sivustoilta: fanart.tv, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Voit määrittää tarkasti, miltä sivustoilta mitäkin tietoa haetaan.&#10;&#10;Ensimmäinen haku tehdään aina lähteestä MusicBrainz. Mikäli allmusic- ja/tai amazon.de-linkkejä ei ole lisätty MusicBrainz-sivustolle, haku ei onnistu (mutta puuttuvien linkkien lisääminen on helppoa).</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Ce collecteur utilise les informations des sites suivant : MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com et amazon.de et télécharge les artwork depuis : fanart.tv, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez spécifier quel site utiliser pour récupérer chaque information.&#10;&#10;Le premier résultat est toujours en provenance de MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où allmusic et/ou amazon.de ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site MusicBrainz, les champs de allmusic.com et/ou amazon.de ne peuvent pas être traités (il est toutefois très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Cet extracteur recueille des informations depuis les sites pris en charge suivants : MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com et amazon.de, alors qu'il récupère les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, last.fm et allmusic.com. Il est possible de configurer champ par champ depuis quel site l'information doit être récupérée.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite sur MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où les liens allmusic et/ou amazon.de ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site de MusicBrainz, les champs provenant de allmusic.com et/ou amazon.de ne peuvent pas être récupérés (il est par contre très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Este scraper obtén a información dende os seguintes sitios: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, mentres que as ilustracións as obtén dende: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pódese definir dende que sitios se obterá a información específica de cada campo.&#10;&#10;A busca inicial faise sempre en MusicBrainz. No caso de non estar engadidas as ligazón de allmusic e/ou amazon.de no sitio de MusicBrainz, os campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazon.de non se poderán obter (aínda que é moi doado engadir as ligazóns).</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, בעוד שמשיכת גרפיקה נעשית דרך: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. יש אפשרות להגדיר את זאת שדה אחר שדה מאיזה אתר ברצונך למשוך את המידע הספציפי.⏎ ⏎ החיפוש הפנימי נעשה תמיד דרך MusicBrainz. במקרה שקישור allmusic לא התווסף באתר MusicBrainz, השדות מאת allmusic.com אינן יכולות להימשך (למרות שזה מאוד קל להוסיף את הקישורים הריקים).</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Ovaj sakupljač prikuplja informacije sa sljedećih podržanih stranica: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com i amazon.de, dok preuzima omote filmova sa: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Može poredati popis stranica iz kojih želite sakupiti informacije jednu iza druge.&#10;&#10;Pretraga uvijek započinje na MusicBrainzu. U slučaju da allmusic i/ili amazon.de poveznice nisu dodane na MusicBrainz stranicu, polja sa allmusic.com i/ili amazon.de ne mogu se nabaviti (ali je vrlo jednostavno moguće dodati te nedostajuće poveznice).</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">A leolvasó szöveges infókat gyűjt a támogatott oldalakról: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, valamint képeket a : fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com-ról. Beállítható hogy honnan, és milyen infót gyűjtsön. A keresés mindig a MusicBrainz-on folyik, de könnyen hozzáadhatjuk a hiányzó találatokat az allmusic.com, vagy az amazon.de-ről.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Pengais ini mengambil informasi dari berbagai situs yang mendukung: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, sembari mengambil artwork dari: fanart.tv, lastfm dan allmusic.com. Ini dapat diatur perbagian dari situ mana informasi tertentu akan diambil.&#10;&#10;Pencarian awal akan dilakukan di MusicBrainz. Apabila tautan dari allmusic dan/atau amazon.de tidak ditambahkan di situs MusicBrainz, bagian dari allmusic.com dan/atau amazon.de tidak dapat ditarik (Namun sangatlah mudah menambahkan tautan tersebut).</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Þessi skafa nær í upplýsingar frá eftirfarandi stöðum sem eru studdir: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de, og nær í myndefni frá: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Hægt er að stilla reit fyrir reit hvaðan upplýsingarnar koma.&#10;&#10;Leitin byrjar alltaf á MusicBrainz. Ef allmusic og/eða amazon.de tenglar eru ekki á MusicBrainz veitunni, næst ekki í upplýsingarnar frá allmusic.com og/eða amazon.de (mjög auðvelt að bæta tenglunum við samt).</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Questo ricercatore prende informazioni dai seguenti siti: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, mentre prende grafica da: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Puoi impostare campo per campo cosa prendere e da dove.⏎ ⏎La ricerca iniziale viene sempre fatta su MusicBrainz. In caso i links a allmusic e/o amazon.de non sono stati messi su MusicBrainz, i campi da questi siti non possono essere recuperati (è molto facile aggiungere quei link, comunque).</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します：MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de。アートワークは以下のサイトから取得します：fanart.tv, last.fm, allmusic.com。各フィールドごとに、どの情報をどのサイトから取得するか、個別に指定することもできます。&#10;&#10;最初は MusicBrainz を使って検索が行われます。MusicBrainz サイトに allmusic や amazon.de のリンクが追加されていない場合は、allmusic.com / amazon.de からのフィールドは取得できません (リンクを追加するのは簡単ですが)。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">이 자료수집기는 다음의 사이트에서 정보를 가져옵니다: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de. 아트워크는 다음의 사이트에서 가져옵니다: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. 특정 정보를 지정한 사이트에서 가져오도록 필드별로 설정할 수 있습니다&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Šis skreperis surenka informaciją iš šių palaikomų puslapių: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ir amazon.de bei atsiunčia iliustracijas iš: fanart.tv, last.fm ir allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatytas laukas po laiko, kad nurodyti iš kokio puslapio paimti konkrečią informaciją.&#10;&#10;Pradinė paieška visada atliekama MusicBrainz puslapyje. Jei kartais allmusic ir/raba amazon.de nuorodos nepridėtos į MusicBrainz puslapį, laukai iš allmusic.com ir/arba amazon.de negalės būti gauti (tačiau labai lengva pridėti tas trūkstamas nuorodas).</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com and amazon.de, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.⏎ ⏎ The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic and/or amazon.de links are not added on the MusicBrainz site, fields from allmusic.com and/or amazon.de cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Pengikis ini mendapatkan maklumat dari laman tersokong berikut: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com dan amazon.de, manakala ia dapatkan kerja seni dari: fanart.tv, last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ia boleh tetapkan medan mengikut medan supaya anda boleh dapatkan maklumat khusus dari laman tertentu.⏎&#10;⏎&#10;Gelintar awalan sentiasa bermula dengan MusicBrainz. Pautan allmusic dan/atau amazon.de tidak ditambah ke laman MusicBrainz, medan dari allmusic.com dan/atau amazon.de sukar didapati.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde sites: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, allmusic.com en amazon.de. Afbeeldingen worden verzameld van de volgende sites: fanart.tv, Last.fm en allmusic.com. Per veld kan aangegeven worden van welke site je de specifieke informatie wil halen. De initiële zoekopdracht wordt altijd gedaan van MusicBrainz.&#10;&#10;In het geval dat links naar allmusic en/of amazon.de niet zijn toegevoegd op de MusicBrainz site, kunnen velden niet worden opgehaald bij deze sites. (Het is niet moeilijk om de ontbrekende links toe te voegen.)</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Denne skraperen innsamler informasjon fra følgende nettsteder: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com og amazon.de, mens den henter grafikk fra: fanart.tv, last.fm og allmusic.com. Du kan selv bestemme hvilken kilde du ønsker å hente informasjon fra.&#10;&#10;Det første søket blir alltid gjort med MusicBrainz. Hvis allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de linker ikke tilgjengelig hos MusicBrainz, kan ikke felter fra allmusic.com og/eller amazon.de hentes (dog er det er veldig lett å legge til de manglende linkene).</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Ten scraper zbiera informacje z następujących stron: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com oraz amazon.de, a grafiki pobiera z: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Dla każdego pola z informacjami można wybrać osobną stronę.&#10;&#10;Początkowe wyszukiwanie jest zawsze wykonywane na MusicBrainz. Gdy linki do allmusic i/lub amazon.de nie są dodane na stronie MusicBrainz, nie można pobrać tych pól z allmusic.com i/lub amazon.de (pomimo to brakujące linki można bardzo łatwo dodać).</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Este colector recolhe informações dos seguintes sítios:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto obtém artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir em cada campo o sítio do qual quer obter as informações. A pesquisa inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. Caso os endereços allmusic e/ou amazon.de não tenham sido adicionados no sítio MusicBrainz, os campos do allmusic.com e/ou amazon.de não serão obtidos (no entanto, é muito fácil adicionar os links em falta). </description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Acest scraper colectează informații de la următoarele site-uri suportate: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com și amazon.de. Elementele de grafica sunt accesate din: fanart.tv, last.fm și allmusic.com. Acesta poate fi setat câmp cu câmp pentru ca informatiile colectate sa fie cele dorite.⏎ &#10;⏎ &#10;Căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna pe MusicBrainz. În cazul în care Allmusic și/sau link-ul amazon.de nu sunt adăugate pe MusicBrainz, câmpurile din allmusic.com și/sau amazon.de nu pot fi colectate (este foarte ușor însă de adăugat aceste legături lipsă).</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Данный скрапер собирает информацию со следующих сайтов:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com и amazon.de, при этом получая обложки из: fanart.tv, last.fm и allmusic.com. Каждое поле можно настроить так, чтобы оно получало желаемую информацию с определенного вами сайта.⏎ ⏎ Начальный поиск всегда проводится на  MusicBrainz. Для allmusic и/или amazon.de ссылки на сайт MusicBrainz отсутствуют, поля с allmusic.com и/или amazon.de не могут быть заполнены (добавить пропущенные ссылки очень просто).</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera informácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com a amazon.de, zatiaľ čo umeleckú grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic a/alebo amazon.de nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com a/alebo amazon.de (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com in amazon.de; grafike prenaša z: fanart.tv, last.fm in allmusic.com. Vsako informacijo lahko prenesete z različne strani.&#10;&#10;Začeno iskanje je vedno na MusicBrainz. V primeru, da na MusicBrainz ni povezave do allmusic.com in/ali amazon.de, informacij od tam ne morete prenesti (a to težavo hitro lahko odpravite).</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com och amazon.de, och konstverk från: fanart.tv, last.fm och allmusic.com. Det kan anges fält för fält vilken sajt du vill få den specifika informationen.⏎ ⏎ Den initiala sökningen är alltid utförd på MusicBrainz sajt, fälten från allmusic.com och/eller amazon.de länkarna läggs inte till på MusicBrainz sajten, fälten från allmusic.com och/eller amazon.de kan inte hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த சுரண்டியானது MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com மற்றும் amazon.de ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். திரை குறும்படங்களை fanart.tv, last.fm மற்றும் allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். ⏎ ⏎ முதன்மை தேடல் எப்போதும் MusicBrainz தான் நடக்கும். allmusic மற்றும் amazon.de சேர்க்கபடாவிட்டால் அவற்றில் இருந்து தகவல்கள் செமிக்கபடமாட்டது (தவறிய இணைப்புகளை சேர்ப்பது மிகவும் எளிது).</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">Bu scraper bilgileri toplamak için şu siteleri desteklemektedir:  MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ve amazon.de, çizimleri için ise: fanart.tv, last.fm ve allmusic.com desteklenmektedir. Her bilginin özellikle nereden alınacağını tek tek ayarlayabilirsiniz.&#10;&#10;İlk olarak arama daima MusicBrainz'de yapılır. MusicBrainz'e allmusic ve/veya amazon.de linkleri eklenmemiş olması durumunda allmusic.com'dan ve/veya amazon.de'den ilgili alanlar alınamaz (gerçi bu eksik linkleri eklemek çok kolaydır).</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Здирач збирає інформацію з наступних сторінок: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com та amazon.de, тоді як отримує обкладинки з: fanart.tv, last.fm та allmusic.com.&#10;&#10;Початковий пошук завжди робиться на MusicBrainz. Якщо посилання з allmusic і/або amazon.de не додаються на сторінку MusicBrainz, тоді поля з allmusic.com і/або amazon.de неможливо отримати (однак дуже легко додати ці пропущені посилання).</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Trình này thu thập thông tin từ những site được hỗ trợ như: MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, amazon.de, và lấy ảnh bìa từ các nguồn: fanart.tv, last.fm và allmusic.com. Bạn có thể tùy chỉnh chọn từng thứ riêng biệt để lấy từ site bạn muốn.\n \n Lần tìm kiếm đầu tiên luôn luôn được sử dụng từ MusicBrainz. Trong trường hợp các link allmusic và/hoặc amazon.de không có trên MusicBrainz, các trường từ allmusic.com và/hoặc amazon.de sẽ không thể lấy về được (tuy nhiên rất dễ để tự thêm vào các link này bằng tay).</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：MusicBrainz、last.fm、allmusic.com 和 amazon.de，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、last.fm 和 allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从 MusicBrainz 获取。如果 MusicBrainz 网站没有到 allmusic 和/或 amazon.de 的外部链接，则无法获取 allmusic.com 的/或 amazon.de 的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">本搜刮器支援從以下網站取得資訊：MusicBrainz、last.fm、allmusic.com和amazon.de，並從以下網站取得專輯照片：fanart.tv、last.fm和allmusic.com。您並可以指定每一項內容的來源網站。&#10;&#10;初始搜尋結果總是先從MusicBrainz取得。如果MusicBrainz網站沒有加入到allmusic和/或amazon.de的外部連結，則無法取得allmusic.com的/或amazon.de的信息(當然您能很輕易地加入遺失的連結)。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=133547</forum>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.artwork.beef" name="Artwork Beef" version="0.28.3" provider-name="rmrector">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.19.0" />
		<import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.20.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="3.3.0" />
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
		<import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.8" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="kodi.context.item">
		<menu id="kodi.core.main">
			<menu id="kodi.core.manage">
				<item library="context.py">
					<label>AB: $ADDON[script.artwork.beef 32410]</label>
					<visible>!Skin.HasSetting(disablecontext:script.artwork.beef) + [StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, musicvideo) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, musicvideo)]</visible>
				</item>
				<item library="context_gui.py">
					<label>AB: $ADDON[script.artwork.beef 32411]</label>
					<visible>!Skin.HasSetting(disablecontext:script.artwork.beef) + [StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, musicvideo) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, musicvideo)]</visible>
				</item>
				<item library="context_debug_remove.py">
					<label>AB: $ADDON[script.artwork.beef 32427]</label>
					<visible>Skin.HasSetting(enablecontext:script.artwork.beef.debug) + [StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, musicvideo) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, season) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, musicvideo) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, season)]</visible>
				</item>
				<item library="context_debug_logitem.py">
					<label>AB: $ADDON[script.artwork.beef 32430]</label>
					<visible>Skin.HasSetting(enablecontext:script.artwork.beef.debug) + [StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode) | StringCompare(ListItem.DBTYPE, musicvideo) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, movie) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, set) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, tvshow) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, episode) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, musicvideo)]</visible>
				</item>
			</menu>
			<item library="context.py">
				<label>AB: $ADDON[script.artwork.beef 32410]</label>
				<visible>!Skin.HasSetting(disablecontext:script.artwork.beef) + [String.StartsWith(System.BuildVersion,18) | String.StartsWith(System.BuildVersion,19)] + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, artist) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, album) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, song)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context_gui.py">
				<label>AB: $ADDON[script.artwork.beef 32411]</label>
				<visible>!Skin.HasSetting(disablecontext:script.artwork.beef) + [String.StartsWith(System.BuildVersion,18) | String.StartsWith(System.BuildVersion,19)] + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, artist) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, album) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, song)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context_debug_remove.py">
				<label>AB: $ADDON[script.artwork.beef 32427]</label>
				<visible>Skin.HasSetting(enablecontext:script.artwork.beef.debug) + [String.StartsWith(System.BuildVersion,18) | String.StartsWith(System.BuildVersion,19)] + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, artist) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, album) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, song)]</visible>
			</item>
			<item library="context_debug_logitem.py">
				<label>AB: $ADDON[script.artwork.beef 32430]</label>
				<visible>Skin.HasSetting(enablecontext:script.artwork.beef.debug) + [String.StartsWith(System.BuildVersion,18) | String.StartsWith(System.BuildVersion,19)] + [String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, artist) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, album) | String.IsEqual(ListItem.DBTYPE, song)]</visible>
			</item>
		</menu>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" start="login" library="service.py" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Automatically adds extra artwork for your media.</summary>
		<description lang="en">Artwork Beef automatically adds extra artwork for TV shows and movies into your library. It grabs them from wonderful web services and the file system.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="en">Artwork sources: fanart.tv, TheTVDB.com, The Movie Database, TheAudioDB, KyraDB</disclaimer>
		<summary lang="es">Agrega automáticamente ilustraciones adicionales para sus medios.</summary>
		<description lang="es">Artwork Beef agrega automáticamente ilustraciones adicionales para Series TV y Películas a su biblioteca. Las ilustraciones son agregadas desde Servicios web y el Sistema de archivos local.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="es">Fuente para ilustraciones: fanart.tv, TheTVDB.com, The Movie Database, TheAudioDB, KyraDB</disclaimer>
		<news>
v0.28.3 (2020-10-21)
- fix: treat 403 as 404 and replace it
- fix: don't throw an error when a movie set is lost

v0.28.2 (2020-08-09)
- Fix: avoid adding duplicate fanart from TVDB
- Fix: log full URL when download fails

v0.28.1 (2020-04-25)
- Fix: remove KyraDB

v0.28.0 (2020-02-08)
- Feature: Add "Path exclusion" settings to skip processing media items by path
		</news>
		<source>https://github.com/rmrector/script.artwork.beef</source>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=258886</forum>
		<website>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/</website>
		<license>The MIT License</license>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<assets>
			<icon>icon.png</icon>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.moviegenreicons.horizon" name="Movie Genre Icons - Horizon" version="0.0.1" provider-name="Swageroni_">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="true" type="moviegenreicons" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Horizon Movie Genre Icons</summary>
		<description lang="en">Movie Genre Icons for Horizon skin</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.tvshows.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database"
       version="3.5.5"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.imdb.com" version="2.9.2"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.tvshows"
             language="en"
             library="tmdb.xml"
             cachepersistence="00:15"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Сваля инф. за ТВ Сериали от TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Stahovač informací k seriálům z TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">TMDB Fernsehserien Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Scraper Τηλ. Σειρών του TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">TMDB TV show Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">TMDB TV show Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Scraper de series TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur de d'émissions télé TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Scraper serie de TV TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">סקרייפר סדרות TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">TMDB sakupljač TV serija</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">TMDB TV show Letöltő</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Pengais Serial TV TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">TMDB TV skafa fyrir sjónvarpsefni</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">TMDB TV 쇼 정보수집기</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">TMDB TV laidų skreperis</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">TMDB TV-serie scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Ekstraktor serialowy TMDB</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Colector de filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper de Seriados TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">TMDB ТВ шоу инфоресурс</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">TMDB TV-serie skrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">TMDB 剧集刮削器</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">themoviedb.org is 'n verniet en oop fliek databasis. Dit is totaal gebruiker gedryf deur mense soos jy. TMDB word huidiglik deur miljoene mense elke maand gebruik, en met hulle kragtige API word dit ook deur baie gewilde media sentrums soos Kodi gebruik om Fliek Metadata, Plakkate en Ondersteunerkuns te onttrek om die gebruiker se ondervinding te verryk.</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">themoviedb.org е безплатна и отворена филмова база данни. Задвижва се изцяло от потребителите си, от хора като вас. Милиони хора по света всеки месец ползват TMDb. Благодарение на многофункционално API може да се ползва от най-различни и популярни медийни центрове като Kodi, които извличат метаданни, постери и фанарт за филмите с цел за красивото оформяне на интерфейса.</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">themoviedb.org és una base de dades oberta i lliure. Es manté completament per usuaris, per gent com tu. TMDb s'utilitza actualment per milions de persones cada mes i amb la seva potent API també és utilitzada per molts centre media populas com l'Kodi per obtenir les meta-dades de pel·lícules, pósters i fanart per enriquir l'experiència d'usuari.</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">themoviedb.org je bezplatná a otevřená databáze filmů a seriálů. Je celá řízena uživateli, tedy lidmi jako vy. TMDb je aktuálně používána každý měsíc milióny lidí a se svým výborným API je také používána mnoha oblíbenými multimediálními centry, jako je Kodi, k získávání metadat, plakátů a fanartů filmů a seriálů pro obohacení uživatelského zážitku.</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mae themoviedb.org yn gronfa ddata ffilmiau rhydd ac agored. Mae'n cael ei yrru gan ddefnyddwyr fel chi. Mae TMDb yn cael ei ddefnyddio gan filiynau o bobl bob mis a gyda'i API pwerus, mae'n cael ei ddefnyddio gan lawer o'r canolfannau cyfrwng fel Kodi i estyn metadata ffilmiau, posteri a chelf er mwyn cyfoethogi profiad defnyddwyr.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">themoviedb.org er en fri og åben filmdatabase. Den er helt og aldeles brugerdrevet af folk som dig. TMDb bruges i dag af millioner af mennesker hver måned, og med deres kraftfulde API er den også brugt af mange populære mediecentre såsom Kodi til at hente metadata, plakater og fankunst til film, for at berige brugerens oplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">TheMovieDB.org ist eine freie und offene Filmdatenbank. Sie wird von Benutzern wie dir angetrieben. TheMovieDB wird zur Zeit von millionen Nutzern jeden Monat genutzt und dank ihrer mächtigen API ist sie auch von vielen Media-Center, wie z.B. Kodi, implementiert, um Film-Metadaten, -Poster und -Fanarts zu beziehen, die das Benutzererlebnis verbessern.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Το themoviedb.org είναι μία δωρεάν και ανοικτή βάση δεδομένων ταινιών. Διαχειρίζεται πλήρως από ανθρώπους σαν και εσάς. Το TMDb χρησιμοποιείται από εκατομμύρια ανθρώπους κάθε μήνα, και με το πανίσχυρο API τους, χρησιμοποιείται και από πολλά δημοφιλή κέντρα πολυμέσων όπως το Kodi για να λαμβάνουν μετα-δεδομένα Ταινιών, Αφίσες και Fanart για εμπλουτισμό της εμπειρίας του χρήστη.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Es una página web que se basa en contenido subido por los usuarios. TMDb es usada diariamente por mucha gente gracias a su API, que es usada por más programas aparte de Kodi para descargar información de películas así como Posters o Fanart (Fondos de escritorio basados en películas usados en distintos skins) para enriquecer la experiencia de usar Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">themovieDB.org es una base de datos de películas gratuita y abierta. Está  formada con contenido subido por usuarios como vos. TMDb es actualmente utilizada por millones de personas cada mes y, gracias a su poderosa API, es usada por muchos programas populares como Kodi para descargar Información de Películas, Posters y Fanart para enriquecer la experiencia de usar Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">themoviedb.org es una base de datos de películas gratis y abierta. Es completamente manejada por usuarios y personas como tu. Actualmente TMDb es usada por millones de personas cada mes, y dado a su poderosa API, es usada también por varios media centers populares como Kodi para obtener Metada de Películas, Posters y Fanarts, enriqueciendo de esta manera la experiencia del usuario.</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">themoviedb.org on tasuta ja vaba juurdepääsuga filmide andmebaas.See on täielikult koostatud sinu sarnaste inimeste poolt. TMDb on hetkel igapäevaselt kasutuses miljonite inimeste poolt ja seda kasutavad paljud populaarsed meediakeskused, nagu ka Kodi, filmiandmete, fännikunsti ja posterite leidmiseks.</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">themoviedb.org on vapaa ja avoin elokuvatietokanta. Se on täysin käyttäjien ylläpitämä. TMDb:a käyttää miljoonat ihmiset joka kuukausi, sitä käytetään käyttäjäkokemuksen rikastuttamiseen monissa muissakin suosituissa Kodi:n kaltaisissa ohjelmissa lataamalla elokuvien tietoja, julisteita ja fanitaidetta.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">themoviedb.org est une base de données gratuite et libre d'accès de films. Elle est totalement gérée par les utilisateurs. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et, grâce à ses puissantes fonctions et routines, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux Media Centers populaires comme Kodi aux fins de récupération des Métadonnées, Posters et Fanarts des films en vue d'améliorer l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">themoviedb.org est une base de données libre et ouverte. Elle est complètement gérée par des gens comme vous. TMDb est actuellement utilisée par des millions de personnes chaque mois et avec son API puissante, elle est également utilisée par de nombreux centres multimédias populaires comme Kodi pour récupérer les métadonnées des films, les affiches et le fanart afin d'enrichir l'expérience de l'utilisateur.</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">themoviedb.org é una base de datos sobre filmes libre e aberta, impulsada por xente coma ti. Na actualidade TMDb é usada por millóns de persoas todos os meses, e grazas ó seu potente API, usado por algúns dos centros multimedia máis populares como Kodi para obter a información dos filmes, Posters e Fanart e así mellorar a experiencia do usuario.</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">themoviedb.org je besplatna i otvorena baza filmskih podataka. TMDb trenutno koriste milijuni ljudi svaki mjesec uz pomoću njegovog snažnog API-ja, isto tako se koristi u mnogim popularnim medijskim centrima poput Kodija, kako bi mogli sakupljati informacije o filmovima, filmske postere, omote filmova i na kraju obogatili korisničko iskustvo.</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">A themoviedb.org egy ingyenes és nyílt filmadatbázis. Teljes egészében olyan felhasználók töltik fel, mint például Te. A TMDb-t havonta emberek milliói használják és a hatékony API-n keresztül számos népszerű média center is, mint például az Kodi a filmadatok, poszterek, fanartképek letöltésére.</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">themoviedb.org adalah database film yang gratis dan terbuka. Ini benar-benar digerakkan oleh orang-orang seperti Anda. TMDb saat ini digunakan oleh jutaan orang setiap bulannya dan dengan APInya yang digdaya, juga digunakan oleh beberapa pusat media seperti Kodi untuk mengambil Metadata Film, Poster dan Fanart untuk menperkaya pengalaman penggunanya.</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">themoviedb.org er frír og opinn gagnagrunnur. Hann er algjörlega rekinn af fólki eins og þér. TMBd er notaður af milljónum manna í hverjum mánuði og með öflugum forritaskilum þeirra (API), er hann líka notaður af mörgum vinsælum heimabíókerfum eins og Kodi til að ná í Ítarupplýsingar yfir Kvikmyndir, Veggspjöld og Fanart til að lífga upplifun notandans.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">themoviedb.org è un database libero e aperto. E' gestito da utenti e persone come te. Viene usato correntemente da millioni di persone ogni mese e con le sue potenti API, è anche utilizzato da molti popolari media centers come Kodi per ottenere Metadati, Posters e Fanart di film per arricchire la loro esperienza utente.</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">themoviedb.org は自由でオープンな映画データベースです。その運営は、完全にユーザ主導で行われています。TMDb は現在毎月何百万人もの人に利用されているほか、Kodi のようなメディアセンターも、TMDb のパワフルな API を介して映画メタデータ、ポスター、ファンアートを取得し、使い勝手を向上させるなどして使っています。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">themoviedb.org 는 전적으로 여러분 같은 이용자가 주도하는 무료 공개 영화 데이터베이스입니다. TMDb 는 현재 매월 수백만의 사람들이 강력한 API와 함께 사용하고 있을 뿐만 아니라 Kodi 같은 많은 미디어 센터가 영화 정보, 포스터, 팬아트를 가져와 풍성한 사용자 경험을 제공하는데 이용되고 있습니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">themoviedb.org yra nemokama ir atvira Filmų duomenų bazė. Jis remiamas ir skaitinamas tokių pat vartotojų kaip ir jūs. TMDb šiuo metu naudoja milijonai žmonių kiekvieną mėnesį, ir turi galingą API (informacinį centrą), taip pat naudojamas daug populiarių žiniasklaidos centrų. Pavyzdžiui Kodi gauti filmo(-ų) metaduomenis, plakatus ir FanArt siekiant praturtinti vartotojo patirtį.</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">themoviedb.org is a free and open movie database. It's completely user driven by people like you. TMDb is currently used by millions of people every month and with their powerful API, it is also used by many popular media centers like Kodi to retrieve Movie Metadata, Posters and Fanart to enrich the user's experience.</description>
    <description lang="ml_IN">മൂവി ഡി ബി, എല്ലാവർക്കും കൈവക്കാവുന്ന ഒരു സൗജന്യ വിവരശേഖരമാണ്. ഇതുമൂലം ലോകം മുഴുവനും സിനിമാ പോസ്റ്ററുകൾ എല്ലവരും കാണുന്നു</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">themoviedb.org adalah pangkalan data cakera terbuka. Ia sepenuhnya dipacu oleh individu seperti anda. TMDb buat masa ini diguna oleh berjuta-juta individu setiap bulan dan dengan API hebat mereka, ia juga digunakan oleh banyak pusat media popular seperti Kodi untuk mendapatkan Data Meta, Poster, Seni Peminat Cereka untuk memperkayakan pengalaman pengguna.</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Themoviedb.org is een vrije en open filmdatabank. Gebruikers zoals jij vormen de motor van deze site. Op dit moment gebruiken elke maand miljoenen mensen TMDb. De krachtige API van de site laat mediacenters zoals Kodi toe om metadata, posters en fanart op te halen en zo de gebruikerservaring te verrijken.</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">themoviedb.org er en gratis og åpen filmdatabase. Den drives helt og fullt av mennesker som deg. TMDb brukes av millioner av mennesker hver måned og med sitt gode API, brukes den også av mange popluære mediasenterløsninger som Kodi for å hente metadata for filmer, plakater og fanart for å gi en bedre brukeropplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">themoviedb.org jest wolną i otwartą filmową bazą danych, zarządzaną przez osoby takie jak Ty. Obecnie odwiedzają ją miliony osób miesięcznie, a dzięki dostępności interfejsu programistycznego jest używana przez wiele centrów multimedialnych takich jak Kodi, jako źródło informacji o filmach, plakatów i tapet.</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">O themoviedb.org é uma base de dados de filmes livre e aberta. É actualizado inteiramente por pessoas como você e usado por milhões todos os meses. Com o poderoso motor de busca disponível, também se tornou no favorito para muitos programas de centro de média, como o popular Kodi, para obter informação, posters e fanart que enriquecem a experiência do utilizador.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">O themoviedb.org é um banco de dados aberto e gratuito. É completamente operado por pessoas como você. O TMDb é atualmente usado por milhares de pessoas a cada mês e com sua poderosa API, é usado por muitas centrais de mídia populares como o Kodi para buscar metadados, cartazes e fanart de filmes para enriquecer a experiência do usuário.</description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">themoviedb.org este o bază de date de filme gratuită și deschisă. Este actualizată de oameni ca și tine. TMDb este curent folosită de milioane de oameni în fiecare lună și datorită API-ului puternic, este de asemena folosită de multe centre media populare ca Kodi pentru a obține informații despre filme, afișe și imagini produse de fani (Fanart) care îmbogățesc experiența utilizatorului.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">themoviedb.org — это бесплатная и открытая база данных фильмов. Она полностью поддерживается обычными людьми. В данный момент сайт TMDb используют миллионы людей каждый месяц, и благодаря мощному API его могут использовать различные популярные медиацентры, такие как Kodi, чтобы получать метаданные, постеры и фанарт для фильмов с целью красивого оформления интерфейса.</description>
    <description lang="se">themoviedb.org är en fri och öppen filmdatabas. Det drivs helt av människor som dig. TMDb används av miljontals människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API, är det också använt av många populära mediacenter som Kodi för att hämta filmmetadata, omslag och fanart för att förgylla användarens upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">themoviedb.org je voľná a otvorená databáza filmov. Je výlučne vedená užívateľmi ako si ty. TMDb je každý mesiac používaná miliónmi ľudí, a vďaka svojmu výkonnému API je veľmi populárna medzi 'media centrami' ako Kodi pre sťahovanie filmových metadát, plagátov a fanartov pre obohatenie  zážitkov.</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">themoviedb.org je brezplačna in prosta baza filmov. Je v celoti ustvarjena s strani uporabnikov kot ste vi. TMDB uporablja miljone ljudi in z njihovo močno API, jo lahko uporabljate tudi v multimedijskih centrih kot Kodi, s tem prenesete informacije o filmih, plakate in ozadja ter s tem popestrite uporabniško izkušnjo.</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">themoviedb.org är en gratis och öppen filmdatabas. Den drivs helt av människor som du. TMDb används för närvarande av miljoner människor varje månad och med deras kraftfulla API används den även av många populära mediacenter som t.ex. Kodi för att hämta metadata om filmer, affischer och fanart för att berika användarens upplevelse.</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">themoviedb.org ஒரு இலவச மற்றும் திறந்த திரைப்பட தரவுத்தளம் ஆகும். இந்த தரவுத்தளம்  முற்றிலும் பயனர் மக்களால் இயக்கப்படுகிறது. TMDb அவர்களது சக்திவாய்ந்த API இனால் தற்போது பல இலட்சக்கணக்கான மக்களால் ஒவ்வொரு மாதமும் பயன்படுத்தப்படுகிறது, இது Kodi போன்ற பல பிரபல ஊடக மையங்களில் பயனர் அனுபவத்தை மேம்படுத்த பயன்படுத்தப்படுகிறது.</description>
    <description lang="th_TH">themoviedb.org เป็นฐานข้อมูลภาพยนตร์ที่ฟรีและเปิดกว้าง. มันถูกขับเคลื่อนจากผู้ใช้ โดยคนเช่นคุณ. TMDb ปัจจุบันมีการใช้โดยคนนับล้านในแต่ละเดือน และมีประสิทธิภาพด้วย API ของพวกเขา , มันยังถูกใช้โดยหลายศูนย์สื่อที่นิยมเช่น Kodi เพื่อดึง อธิบายข้อมูลภาพยนตร์, โปสเตอร์และ แฟนอาร์ต เพื่อเพิ่มประสบการณ์ของผู้ใช้</description>
    <description lang="tr_TR">themoviedb.org ücretsiz ve herkese açık bir film veri tabanıdır. Tamamen kullanıcılar tarafından oluşturulmakta ve yönetilmektedir. TMDb her ay milyonlarca kullanıcı tarafından kullanılmakta ve güçlü API'si sayesinde Kodi gibi bir çok popüler medya merkezi tarafından Film Veritabanı, Poster ve Fanart bilgilerini kullanarak kullanıcı deneyimini zenginleştirmektedir.</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">themoviedb.org - це безкоштовна і відкрита база даних фільмів. Вона повністю підтримується звичайними людьми. В даний момент сайт TMDb використовують мільйони людей кожен місяць, і завдяки потужному API, його можуть використовувати різні популярні медіацентри, такі як Kodi, щоб отримувати метадані, постери і фанарт для фільмів з метою оформлення інтерфейсу.</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">themoviedb.org là cơ sở dữ liệu về phim ảnh mở và miễn phí. Nó hoàn toàn được kiểm soát bởi những người như bạn. TMDb hiện tại đang được sử dụng bởi hàng triệu người dùng hàng tháng và với sự hỗ trợ của bộ API mạnh mẽ nó cũng được sử dụng bởi những thiết bị giải trí cá nhân như Kodi cho việc lấy dữ liệu về Phim ảnh, Poster và Fanart để làm tăng trải nghiệm của người sử dụng</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">themoviedb.org 是一个开放和自由的电影数据库。它完全由象你一样的用户来掌控。TMDb 每月为上百万用户提供服务，并通过强大的 API 界面为许多流行的媒体中心系统如 Kodi 提供电影资料、封面海报和同人画以丰富用户的体验。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">themoviedb.org是一個免費和開放的電影資料庫。它是完全由與您一樣的廣大使用者來更新資訊。 TMDb目前擁有數以百萬計的使用人次並且有著強大的API，許多受歡迎的媒體中心平台像Kodi藉由TMDb獲取電影的數據資料庫，海報和影片資訊，以豐富使用者體驗。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=200504</forum>
    <website>https://www.themoviedb.org/</website>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.beautifulsoup"
       name="BeautifulSoup"
       version="3.2.1"
       provider-name="Leonard Richardson (leonardr@segfault.org)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python"
    		version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>HTML/XML parser for quick-turnaround applications like screen-scraping</summary>
    <description>Beautiful Soup parses arbitrarily invalid SGML and provides a variety of methods and Pythonic idioms for iterating and searching the parse tree.</description>
    <license>BSD</license>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.marcelveldt" version="1.0.2" name="Marcelveldt's BETA repository" provider-name="marcelveldt, finkleandeinhorn">

	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Marcelveldt's BETA repository">
		<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kodi-community-addons/repository.marcelveldt/master/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kodi-community-addons/repository.marcelveldt/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kodi-community-addons/repository.marcelveldt/master/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Kodi repository for beta/test versions of Marcelveldt's addons</summary>
		<description lang="en">Kodi repository for beta/test versions of Marcelveldt's addons, for stable versions please just use the official Kodi repository. This repo is for test/beta versions of my work only</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.artists.universal"
       name="Universal Artist Scraper"
       version="4.3.3"
       provider-name="Olympia, Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="3.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="2.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.artists"
             language="en"
             library="artistuniversal.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af_ZA">Universal Skraper vir Kunstenaars</summary>
    <summary lang="ar_SA">ماسحة الفنان العالمية</summary>
    <summary lang="be_BY">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="bg_BG">Универсален източник за информация за артисти</summary>
    <summary lang="ca_ES">Arreplegador universal per artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="cs_CZ">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro umělce</summary>
    <summary lang="cy_GB">Crafwr Cyffredinol ar gyfer Artistiaid</summary>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Universel Scraper til Kunstnere</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Universeller Scraper für Interpreten</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Universal Scraper Καλλιτεχνών</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Scraper universal para artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal de Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="et_EE">Universaalne artistide kraabits</summary>
    <summary lang="fi_FI">Universaali artistien tiedonhakija</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">Collecteur universel d'artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Extracteur universel pour les artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="gl_ES">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="he_IL">Universa סקרייפר אמנים</summary>
    <summary lang="hr_HR">Univerzalni sakupljač informacija izvođača</summary>
    <summary lang="hu_HU">Univerzális előadó leolvasó</summary>
    <summary lang="id_ID">Pengais Universal untuk Artis</summary>
    <summary lang="is_IS">Almenn skafa fyrir Listamenn</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Scraper universale degli artisti</summary>
    <summary lang="ja_JP">汎用アーティストスクレーパー</summary>
    <summary lang="ko_KR">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="lt_LT">Universalus Artistų Scrapers</summary>
    <summary lang="lv_LV">Mākslinieku universālais skrāpis</summary>
    <summary lang="mk_MK">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="ms_MY">Pengikis Universal untuk Artis</summary>
    <summary lang="my_MM">အနုပညာရှင်များအတွက် Universal Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="nl_NL">Universele scraper voor artiesten</summary>
    <summary lang="nb_NO">Universalskraper for artister</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Universal Scraper informacji o artystach muzycznych</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_PT">Colector universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="ro_RO">Scraper universal pentru artisti</summary>
    <summary lang="ru_RU">Универсальный скрапер для исполнителей</summary>
    <summary lang="sk_SK">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre umelcov</summary>
    <summary lang="sl_SI">Univerzalen ponudnik informacij o izvajalcih</summary>
    <summary lang="sv_SE">Universiell artistskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">கலைஞர்களின் ஒட்டு மொத்தமான சுரண்டி</summary>
    <summary lang="tr_TR">Sanatçılar için Evrensel Scraper</summary>
    <summary lang="uk_UA">Універсальний здирач для виконавців</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Trình lấy dữ liệu Nghệ sĩ từ nhiều nguồn</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_CN">通用艺术家信息刮削器</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">通用演出者訊息搜括器</summary>
    <description lang="af_ZA">Hierdie skraper versamel informasie van die volgende ondersteunde werwe: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, en allmusic.com, terwyl kunswerke gryp van: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm en allmusic.com. Dit kan veld vir veld gestel word vanaf watter werf jy die spesifike informasie wil hê.&#10;&#10;Die aanvanklike soektog word altyd op MusicBrainz gedoen. Ingeval die allmusic skakel nie bygevoeg is op die MusicBrainz werf, kan velde van allmusic.com nie gaan haal word nie (egter baie maklik om daardie ontbrekende skakels by te voeg).</description>
    <description lang="ar_SA">هذه الماسحة تجمع المعلومات من المواقع المدعومة التالية: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, في حين تأخذ عناوين الأعمال الفنية من: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. يمكن أن ترتب حقل تلو حقل حسب الموقع الذي تريد منه تلك المعلومة المحددة.&#10;&#10;البحث الابتدائي يتم دائما على ميوزك برينز. في حال أن رابط كل الموسيقى غير مضاف على حقول موقع ميوزك برينز من allmusic.com لا يمكن الحصول عليها(على الرغم من سهولة إضافة هذه الروابط المفقودة).</description>
    <description lang="be_BY">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="bg_BG">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не е налична препратка към allmusic.com на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com става невъзможно (добавянето на препратка е много лесно).</description>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs suportats</description>
    <description lang="cs_CZ">Tento zdroj dat získává informace z následujících podporovaných stránek: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Lze nastavit jakou informaci stahovat z jakých stránek.&#10;&#10;Základní hledání je vždy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že schází odkaz allmusic na stránce MusicBrains, nelze stáhnout informace z allmusic.com (avšak je velmi snadné chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
    <description lang="cy_GB">Mae'r crafwr yn casglu gwybodaeth o'r gwefannau canlynol:  TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, a allmusic.com, tra'n cipio gwaith celf o: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Mae modd ei osod fesul maes i ddewis pa wefan i gasglu gwybodaeth benodol.&#10;&#10;Bydd y chwilio cychwynnol yn cael ei wneud ar MusicBrainz. Rhag ofn nad yw dolen allmusic wedi ei osod ar wefan MusicBrainz nid oes modd estyn meysydd o allmusic.com (mae'n hawdd gosod y dolenni coll hynny).</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, og allmusic.com, og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Det kan vælges felt for felt, fra hvilke sider du ønsker, at få de pågældende informationer fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic linket er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Dieser Scaper sammelt Informationen von den folgenden, unterstützten Seiten: MusicBrainz, Last.fm, Allmusic.com und Amazon.de. Es werden dabei Grafiken von den folgenden Seiten geladen: Fanart.tv, Last.fm und Allmusic.com. Von welcher Seite die Informationen geladen werden, kann einzeln konfiguriert werden.⏎ &#10;⏎&#10;Die initialie Suche wird immer über MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollten keine Allmusic- und/oder Amazon.de-Links auf der MusicBrainz-Seite gesetzt worden sein, können Felder von Allmusic.com und/oder Amazon.de nicht geladen werden (fehlende Links können jedoch sehr einfach hinzugefügt werden).</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Αυτό το scraper συλλέγει πληροφορίες από τις ακόλουθες υποστηριζόμενες ιστοσελίδες: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm και allmusic.com, ενώ λαμβάνει εικόνες από τα: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm και allmusic.com. Μπορεί να οριστεί πεδίο ανά πεδίο αναλόγως των πληροφοριών που επιθυμείτε από την εκάστοτε ιστοσελίδα.&#10;&#10;Η αρχική αναζήτηση γίνεται πάντα στο MusicBrainz. Σε περίπτωση που δεν έχουν προστεθεί σύνδεσμοι για το allmusic στο MusicBrainz, δε θα μπορούν να ληφθούν πεδία από το allmusic.com (ωστόσο είναι πολύ εύκολο να προστεθούν αυτοί οι ελλιπείς σύνδεσμοι).</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Este scraper recopila información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Este scraper recopila información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras que obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
    <description lang="et_EE">See kraabits kogub infot järgmistelt lehtedelt: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm ja allmusic.com, pilte: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm ja allmusic.com. Saad välja kaupa määrata, milliselt lehelt mis infot soovid.&#10;&#10;Esmane otsing tehakse alati saidilt MusicBrainz. Kui MusicBrainz lehele pole allmusic  linki lisatud, siis allmusic.com lehelt sisu hankida ei saa (puuduvaid linke saad ise lihtsalt lisada).</description>
    <description lang="fi_FI">Tämä tiedonhakija käyttää tietolähteinään seuraavia sivustoja: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Kuvat ja grafiikat haetaan seuraavilta sivustoilta: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Voit määrittää tarkasti, miltä sivustoilta mitäkin tietoa haetaan.&#10;&#10;Ensimmäinen haku tehdään aina lähteestä MusicBrainz. Mikäli allmusic-linkkiä ei ole lisätty MusicBrainz-sivustolle allmusic.com-osoitteessa, haku ei onnistu (mutta puuttuvien linkkien lisääminen on helppoa).</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Ce collecteur répertorie les informations des sites suivants : TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, Last.fm et allmusic.com tout en assemblant les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez définir la source d'information pour chaque champ.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite à partir de MusicBrainz. xxxxxxxx (en attente du retour de l'équipe Kodi) xxxxxxxxxxx</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Cet extracteur recueille des informations depuis les sites pris en charge suivants : TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm et allmusic.com, alors qu'il récupère les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm et allmusic.com. Il est possible de configurer champ par champ depuis quel site l'information doit être récupérée.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite sur MusicBrainz. Dans le cas où les liens allmusic ne sont pas ajoutés sur le site de MusicBrainz, les champs provenant de allmusic.com ne peuvent pas être récupérés (il est par contre très simple d'ajouter ces liens manquants).</description>
    <description lang="gl_ES">Este scraper recolle información dos seguintes sitios:&#10;TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm e allmusic.com, mentres que, obtén as imaxes de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir en cada campo o sitio de onde quere obter a información.&#10;&#10;A busca inicial é feita sempre no MusicBrainz, no caso de que a ligazón a allmusic non se teña engadido nos campos do sítio MusicBrainz dende allmusic.com, non se poderán obter (aínda que, é moi doado engadir as ligazóns que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="he_IL">סקרייפר זה אוסף מידע מהתארים הנתמכים הבאים: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, בעוד שמשיכת גרפיקה נעשית דרך: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. יש אפשרות להגדיר את זאת שדה אחר שדה מאיזה אתר ברצונך למשוך את המידע הספציפי.⏎ ⏎ החיפוש הפנימי נעשה תמיד דרך MusicBrainz. במקרה שקישור allmusic לא התווסף באתר MusicBrainz, השדות מאת allmusic.com אינן יכולות להימשך (למרות שזה מאוד קל להוסיף את הקישורים הריקים).</description>
    <description lang="hr_HR">Ovaj sakupljač prikuplja informacije sa sljedećih podržanih stranica: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm i allmusic.com, dok preuzima omote filmova sa: fanart.tv, last.fm i allmusic.com. Može poredati popis stranica iz kojih želite sakupiti informacije jednu iza druge.\n&#10;\n&#10;Pretraga uvijek započinje na MusicBrainzu. U slučaju da allmusic poveznica nije dodana na MusicBrainz stranicu, polja sa allmusic.com ne mogu se nabaviti (ali je vrlo jednostavno moguće dodati te nedostajuće poveznice).</description>
    <description lang="hu_HU">Ez a leolvasó a következő weboldalakról gyűjti be az adatokat:  TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm és allmusic.com, míg képeket a következő oldalakról gyűjt: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm és allmusic.com. Egyenként beállítható, hogy az adott mezőt melyik weboldalról töltse fel⏎ ⏎ A kiinduló keresés mindig a MusicBrainz. Amennyiben az allmusic utalás nincs hozzáadva MusicBrainz oldalhoz, a mezők nem tölthetők le az allmusic.com oldalról (a hiányzó utalások hozzáadása azonban nagyon egyszerű).</description>
    <description lang="id_ID">Pengais ini mengambil informasi dari berbagai situs yang mendukung: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm dan allmusic.com, sembari mengambil artwork dari: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com. last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ini dapat diatur perbagian dari situ mana informasi tertentu akan diambil.&#10;&#10;Pencarian awal akan dilakukan di MusicBrainz. Apabila tautan dari allmusic belum ditambahkan di situs MusicBrainz, bagian dari allmusic.com tidak dapat ditarik (Namun sangatlah mudah menambahkan tautan tersebut).</description>
    <description lang="is_IS">Þessi skafa safnar sama upplýsingum frá eftirfarandi studdum stöðum: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, og allmusic.com, og á meðan nær hún í myndir frá: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Hægt er að stilla reit fyrir reit hvaðan upplýsingarnar koma.&#10;&#10;Leitin byrjar alltaf á MusicBrainz. Ef allmusic tenglar eru ekki á MusicBrainz veitunni, næst ekki í upplýsingarnar frá allmusic.com (mjög auðvelt að bæta tenglunum við samt).</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Lo scraper colleziona informazioni da questi siti supportati: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, e allmusic.com, mentre ottiene le grafiche da: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Può essere impostato campo per campo da quale sito vuoi la specifica informazione.&#10;&#10;La ricerca iniziale è sempre fatta su MusicBrainz. Nel caso che il link allmusic non è stato aggiunto al campo del sito MusicBrainz da allmusic.com; non possono essere ottenute (è comunque veramente facile aggiungere questi link mancanti).</description>
    <description lang="ja_JP">このスクレーパーは、以下のサイトから情報を取得します：TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com。アートワークは以下のサイトから取得します：fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm, allmusic.com。各フィールドごとに、どの情報をどのサイトから取得するか、個別に指定することもできます。&#10;&#10;最初は MusicBrainz を使って検索が行われます。MusicBrainz サイトに allmusic のリンクが追加されていない場合は、allmusic.com からのフィールドは取得できません (リンクを追加するのは簡単ですが)。</description>
    <description lang="ko_KR">이 자료수집기는 다음의 사이트에서 정보를 가져옵니다: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com.아트워크는 다음의 사이트에서 가져옵니다: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm, allmusic.com. 특정 정보를 지정한 사이트에서 가져오도록 필드별로 설정할 수 있습니다.&#10;&#10;초기 검색은 항상 MusicBrainz에서 수행합니다. allmusic 링크가 MusicBrainz 사이트의 필드에 추가되어 있지 않은 경우 정보를 가져올 수 없습니다(누락된 링크는 쉽게 추가할 수 있습니다).</description>
    <description lang="lt_LT">Šis Scrapers renka informaciją iš šių palaikomų svetainių: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, ir allmusic.com, ir atsiunčia meno kūrinius iš: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm ir allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatyti lauko srityje, kurioje svetainėje norite, kad konkrečiu atveju pradinė informacijos pradinis paieška visada bus atlikta remiantis MusicBrainz. Allmusic nuoroda įdėta į MusicBrainz vietoje laukų allmusic.com negali būti (nors tas trūkstamas grandis labai lengva įtraukti).</description>
    <description lang="mk_MK">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="ms_MY">Pengikis ini mendapatkan maklumat dari laman tersokong berikut: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm dan allmusic.com, manakala ia dapatkan kerja seni dari: fanart.tv, htbckdrops.com, last.fm dan allmusic.com. Ia boleh tetapkan medan mengikut medan supaya anda boleh dapatkan maklumat khusus dari laman tertentu.⏎&#10;⏎&#10;Gelintar awalan sentiasa bermula dengan MusicBrainz. Pautan allmusic tidak ditambah ke laman MusicBrainz, medan dari allmusic.com sukar didapati.</description>
    <description lang="my_MM">ဒီ Scraper သည် အချက်အလက်များကို အောက်ဖော်ပြပါ ထောက်ပံ့ထားသော ဆိုဒ်များမှ စုဆောင်းပါသည်။ ထိုဆိုဒ်များမှာ TheAudioDb.com,MusicBrainz,last..fm, နှင့် allmusic.com တို့ဖြစ်သည်။</description>
    <description lang="nl_NL">Deze scraper verzamelt informatie van de volgende ondersteunde websites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, en allmusic.com en tevens pakt hij afbeeldingen van fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm en allmusic.com. Het is mogelijk om per veld aan te geven van welke website je de specifieke informatie wilt halen.&#10;&#10;De initiële zoekopdracht wordt altijd uitgevoerd op MusicBrainz. Wanneer de allmusic link niet is toegevoegd in de juiste velden op de MusicBrainz website kan de informatie van allmusic.com niet worden opgehaald. (Het is erg makkelijk om deze ontbrekende links toe te voegen.)</description>
    <description lang="nb_NO">Denne skraperen samler informasjon fra følgende støttede steder: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm og allmusic.com, mens den henter artwork fra: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Du kan stegvis velge hvilken kilde du ønsker og hente spesifikk informasjon fra.&#10;&#10;Det første søket er alltid gjort hos MusicBrainz. I tilfeller hvor allmusic-linker ikke er lagt til hos MusicBrainz-siden, kan ikke felter fra allmusic.com hentes (det er veldig lett å legge til de manglende linkene).</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Ten ekstraktor pobiera informacje z następujących stron: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, a grafiki pobiera z: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm i allmusic.com. Dla każdego pola z informacjami można wybrać osobną stronę.&#10;&#10;Początkowe wyszukiwanie jest zawsze wykonywane w serwisie MusicBrainz. Gdy wyszukiwanie nie jest wskazane na stronę MusicBrainz, następuje przeszukiwanie serwisu allmusic.com (brakujące linki można łatwo dodać później).</description>
    <description lang="pt_PT">Este colector recolhe informações dos seguintes sítios:&#10;TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm e allmusic.com, enquanto obtém artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm e allmusic.com. Pode definir em cada campo o sítio de onde quer obter as informações. &#10;&#10;A pesquisa inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. Caso um endereço allmusic não tenha sido adicionado no sítio MusicBrainz, os campos do allmusic.com não serão obtidos (no entanto, é muito fácil adicionar os links em falta).</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
    <description lang="ro_RO">Acest scraper colectează informații de la următoarele site-uri suportate: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, și allmusic.com, și opere de artă de la: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm și allmusic.com. Poate fi setat câmp cu câmp de pe care site-ul doriți informații specifice ⏎ ⏎ căutarea inițială se face întotdeauna face pe MusicBrainz.. În cazul în care link-ul Allmusic nu este adăugat la MusicBrainz, allmusic.com nu poate fi folosit (însă este relativ ușor să adăugați aceste link-uri lipsă).</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Этот скрапер собирает информацию со следующих сайтов: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm и allmusic.com, при этом получая обложки с: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm и allmusic.com. Каждое поле может быть настроено для получения определенной информации с желаемого вами сайта.⏎ ⏎ Первичный поиск всегда производится на MusicBrainz. Если линк для allmusic не добавлен на сайте MusicBrainz, то поля с allmusic.com не могут быть заполнены (добавить отсутствующие ссылки очень легко).</description>
    <description lang="sk_SK">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera infomácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm a allmusic.com. Grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
    <description lang="sl_SI">Ta ponudnik združuje informacije s sledečih strani: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm in allmusic.com; grafike prenaša z: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm in allmusic.com. Vsako informacijo lahko prenesete z različne strani.&#10;&#10;Začeno iskanje je vedno na MusicBrainz. V primeru, da na MusicBrainz ni povezave do allmusic.com, informacij od tam ne morete prenesti (a to težavo hitro lahko odpravite).</description>
    <description lang="sv_SE">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm och allmusic.com, medans den samlar konstverk från: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm och allmusic.com. Du kan ange fält för fält från vilken sajt du vill ha den specifika inforamtionen från. Den initiala sökningen är alltid gjord på MusicBrainz. Om inte allmusic.com länken läggs till på MusicBrainz sajten, kan inte fält från allmusic.com hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த சுரண்டியானது TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். திரை குறும்படங்களை fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm மற்றும் allmusic.com ஆகிய இணையதளத்தில் இருந்து தகவல்களை சேகரிக்கும். ⏎ ⏎ முதன்மை தேடல் எப்போதும் MusicBrainz தான் நடக்கும். allmusic மற்றும் amazon.de சேர்க்கபடாவிட்டால் அவற்றில் இருந்து தகவல்கள் செமிக்கபடமாட்டது (தவறிய இணைப்புகளை சேர்ப்பது மிகவும் எளிது).</description>
    <description lang="uk_UA">Здирач збирає інформацію з наступних сторінок: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm та allmusic.com, тоді як отримує обкладинки з: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm та allmusic.com. Для кожного поля можно вказати з якої сторінки ви бажаєте його заповнити.&#10;&#10;Початковий пошук завжди робиться на MusicBrainz. Якщо посилання з allmusic не додаються на сторінку MusicBrainz, тоді поля з allmusic.com неможливо отримати (однак дуже легко додати ці пропущені посилання).</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Trình này thu thập thông tin từ những site được hỗ trợ như: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com, và lấy ảnh bìa từ các nguồn: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm và allmusic.com. Bạn có thể tùy chỉnh chọn từng thứ riêng biệt để lấy từ site bạn muốn.\n \n Lần tìm kiếm đầu tiên luôn luôn được sử dụng từ MusicBrainz. Trong trường hợp các link allmusic không có trên MusicBrainz, các trường từ allmusic.com sẽ không thể lấy về được (tuy nhiên rất dễ để tự thêm vào các link này bằng tay).</description>
    <description lang="zh_CN">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：TheAudioDb.com、MusicBrainz、last.fm 和 allmusic.com，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、htbackdrops.com、last.fm 和 allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从 MusicBrainz 获取，如果 MusicBrainz 网站未加入到 allmusic 的外部链接，则无法获取 allmusic.com 的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">本搜刮器支援從以下網站取得資訊：TheAudioDb.com、MusicBrainz、last.fm和allmusic.com，並從以下網站取得專輯圖片：fanart.tv、htbackdrops.com、last.fm和allmusic.com。您可以指定每一項內容的來源網站。&#10;&#10;初始搜尋結果總是先從MusicBrainz取得，如果MusicBrainz網站未加入到allmusic的外部連結，則無法取得allmusic.com的資訊 (當然您能很輕易地加入遺失的連結)。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL v2.0</license>
    <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=132623</forum>
    <assets>
        <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.exodusredux" name="Exodus Redux Repo" version="0.0.8" provider-name="I-A-C">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Exodus Redux Repo">
	<dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/I-A-C/zips/master/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/I-A-C/zips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/I-A-C/zips/master/</datadir>
	</dir>
    <dir>
        <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml</info>
        <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
        <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/a4k-openproject/repository.openscrapers/master/zips/</datadir>
    </dir>
	<dir>
		<info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/jsergio123/zips/master/</datadir>
	</dir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Exodus Redux is a educational add-on. We do not host any of the contents streamed.</summary>
		<description lang="en"></description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="metadata.common.themoviedb.org"
       name="The Movie Database Scraper Library"
       version="3.2.6"
       provider-name="Team Kodi">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.library"
             library="tmdb.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <summary lang="bg">Библиотека за сваляне на инф. от TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="en">TMDb Scraper Library</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper de peliculas de TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">TMDb elokuvatietojen lataajan kirjasto</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Scraper TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">TMDb leolvasó-könyvtár</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">TMDb-scraperfuncties</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Scraper biblioteki TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Scraper de filmes TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Bibliotecă catalog TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обработчик для TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="se">Skrapebibliotek för TMDb</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">TMDb刮削器代码库</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля миниатюри и fanarts от www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="en">Download thumbs and fanarts from www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga posters y fanart de www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="fi">Lataa pienoiskuvia ja fanitaidetta www.themoviedb.org -sivustolta</description>
    <description lang="fr">Télécharge vignettes et backdrops depuis www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="hu">Bélyeg- és fanartképek letöltése a www.themoviedb.org webhelyről</description>
    <description lang="nl">Miniaturen en fanart ophalen van www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="pl">Pobieraj ikony i fanarty z www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="pt">Descarregar informação de filmes de www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="ro">Descărcați miniaturi și imagini realizate de fani de pe www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="ru">Загружать миниатюры и фанарт с www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="se">Ladda ner miniatyrer och fanart från www.themoviedb.org</description>
    <description lang="zh">从www.themoviedb.org下载海报和同人画</description>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.thecrew" name="[COLOR orchid]THE CREW MODULE[/COLOR]" version="0.0.95" provider-name="The Crew">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">The Crew is a team of individuals that does what it can to provide others, you the best in entertainment.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Many come, Many go. The true and dedicated are here.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author of this addon do not host any of the content which is found and have no affiliation with any of the content providers. This addon simply searches websites for content. Use at your own risk!</disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.studios.white" name="Studio Icons - White" version="0.0.25" provider-name="Team Kodi">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="true" type="studios" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">White Studio Icons</summary>
		<description lang="en">White Studio Icons</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 3.0 United States</license>
	</extension>
</addon>

    <addon id="repository.Atrion18B" name="[COLOR darkgreen]Atrion's Repo for Kodi 18.x Backup[/COLOR]" version="0.6.3" provider-name="Atrion Darnay">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Atrions Repo">
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Atrion/Kodi_18_Repo/master/_repo/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Atrion/Kodi_18_Repo/master/_repo/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Atrion/Kodi_18_Repo/master/_repo/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary>Atrion's Repo for Kodi 18.x</summary>
            <description>Atrion's Repo for Kodi 18.x</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.skinbackgrounds.titanium" name="Skin Backgrounds - Titanium" version="1.0.0" provider-name="marcelveldt">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false" type="skinbackgrounds" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Skin Backgrounds Pack - Titanium</summary>
		<description lang="en">Skin Backgrounds Pack - Titanium</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.skinvariables"
version="0.2.4"
name="Skin Variables"
provider-name="jurialmunkey">
<requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.26.0"/>
</requires>
<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py" />
<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <summary lang="en_GB">Skin Variables helps skinners to construct variables and expressions for multiple containers and listitems using a template</summary>
  <description lang="en_GB">Skin Variables helps skinners to construct variables and expressions for multiple containers and listitems using a template</description>
  <disclaimer lang="en_GB">For skinners</disclaimer>
  <license>GPL-3.0</license>
  <assets>
    <icon>icon.png</icon>
    <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
  </assets>
  <news>0.2.1 - Improve variable build speed</news>
</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.arctic.zephyr.2" name="Arctic Zephyr 2" provider-name="jurialmunkey" version="0.9.62.1">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.14.0" />
        <import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.4.0" />
        <import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="0.0.5" />
        <import addon="plugin.program.autocompletion" version="1.0.1" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper" version="1.0.0" />
        <import addon="resource.images.studios.white" version="0.0.10" />
        <import addon="resource.images.moviegenreicons.transparent" version="0.0.6" />
        <import addon="resource.images.weathericons.outline-hd" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.weathericons.white" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.moviecountryicons.maps" version="0.0.1" />
    </requires>
    <extension debugging="false" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1" point="xbmc.gui.skin">
        <res aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" height="1080" width="1920" />
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="de">Klar, minimalistisch, elegant, einfach, leicht</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_AU">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Limpio, minimalista, elegante, simple, ligero.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Clair, minimaliste, élégant, simple et léger.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Net, minimal, élégant, simple, léger.</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Pulita, minimale, elegante, semplice, leggera.</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">Švari, minimali, elegantiška, paprasta, lengva.</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Schoon, minimaal, elegant, simpel, licht.</summary>
        <summary lang="no">Rent, minimalt, elegant, enkelt, lett.</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Prosta, minimalista, elegancka i lekka</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Limpa, simplista, elegante, leve.</summary>
        <summary lang="ro">Curat, minimalist, elegant, simplu, ușor</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Опрятный, минималистичный, элегантный, простой, светлый.</summary>

        <description lang="en">Arctic Zephyr 2 is a minimalistic skin created by jurialmunkey. The skin is designed to be simple so that the user can focus on their media content. In addition to the default light colour scheme, the skin also includes a number of darker variations.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial Share-Alike 4.0</license>
        <forum />
        <source />
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.weathericons.outline-hd" name="Weather Icons - Outline HD" version="0.0.3" provider-name="braz">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="true" type="weather" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Outline HD Weather Icons</summary>
		<description lang="en">Weather Icons in an outline style, based on the weather icons project by Erik Flowers. http://erikflowers.github.io/weather-icons/</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>Creative Commons Attribution 3.0</license>
		<forum></forum>
		<website></website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/bryanbrazil/resource.images.weathericons.outline-hd</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.inputstreamhelper" name="InputStream Helper" version="0.5.1" provider-name="emilsvennesson, dagwieers, mediaminister, horstle">
  <requires>
    <!--py3 compliant-->
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.pysocks" version="1.6.8" optional="true"/>
  </requires>
  <!-- This is needed to get an add-on icon -->
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module" library="lib"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Kodi InputStream and DRM playback made easy</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">Kodi InputStream und DRM Wiedergabe einfach gemacht</summary>
    <summary lang="el_GR">Βοηθός Inputstream για το Kodi και εύκολη αναπαραγωγή DRM</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_FR">La lecture Kodi InputStream et DRM en toute simplicité</summary>
    <summary lang="es_ES">Kodi InputStream y reproducción DRM echa fácil</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">A simple Kodi module that makes life easier for add-on developers relying on InputStream based add-ons and DRM playback.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Dieses einfache Kodi-Modul macht das Leben für Addon Entwickler einfacher, die auf InputStream basierte Addons und DRM Wiedergabe angewiesen sind.</description>
    <description lang="el_GR">Μία απλή μονάδα για το Kodi η οποία διευκολύνει την ζωή των προγραμματιστών οι οποίοι εξαρτώνται από τα πρόσθετσ InputStream και αναπαραγωγή τύπου DRM.</description>
    <description lang="ru_RU">Простой модуль для Kodi, который облегчает жизнь разработчикам дополнений, с использованием InputStream дополнений и воспроизведения DRM контента.</description>
    <description lang="fr_FR">Un simple module Kodi qui simplifie la vie des développeurs de modules complémentaires en s’appuyant sur des modules complémentaires basés sur InputStream et sur la lecture de DRM.</description>
    <description lang="es_ES">Un módulo Kodi simple que hace la vida más fácil para los desarrolladores de complementos que dependen de complementos basados en InputStream y reproducción de DRM.</description>
    <news>
v0.5.1 (2020-10-02)
- Fix incorrect ARM HWIDs: PHASER and PHASER360
- Added Hebrew translations
- Updated Dutch, Japanese and Korean translations

v0.5.0 (2020-06-25)
- Extract Widevine CDM directly from Chrome OS, minimizing disk space usage and eliminating the need for root access
- Improve progress dialog while extracting Widevine CDM on ARM devices
- Support resuming interrupted downloads on unreliable internet connections
- Reshape InputStream Helper information dialog
- Updated Dutch, English, French, German, Greek, Hungarian, Romanian, Russian, Spanish and Swedish translations
    </news>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://github.com/emilsvennesson/script.module.inputstreamhelper/wiki</website>
    <source>https://github.com/emilsvennesson/script.module.inputstreamhelper</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.six"
       name="six"
       version="1.13.0"
       provider-name="gutworth">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python"
    		version="2.14.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Python 2 and 3 compatibility utilities.</summary>
    <description lang="en">Six is a Python 2 and 3 compatibility library. It provides utility functions for smoothing over the differences between the Python versions with the goal of writing Python code that is compatible on both Python versions. See the documentation for more information on what is provided.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <source>https://pypi.org/project/six/</source>
    <website>https://pypi.org/project/six/</website>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.moviegenreicons.transparent" name="Movie Genre Icons - Transparent" version="0.0.6" provider-name="Team Kodi">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="true" type="moviegenreicons" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Transparent Movie Genre Icons</summary>
		<description lang="en">Movie Genre Icons with a transparent background</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="resource.images.skinicons.wide" name="Skin Icons - Wide" version="1.0.5" provider-name="marcelveldt, cartman.dos">
	<extension point="kodi.resource.images" compile="false" type="skinicons" />
	<requires>
		<import addon="kodi.resource" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en">Skin Icons Pack - Wide</summary>
		<description lang="en">Skin Icons Pack - Wide</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>GPL v3.0</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=334820</forum>
		<website></website>
		<source>https://github.com/cartmandos/resource.images.skinicons.wide/</source>
	</extension>
</addon>

    <addon id="repository.Atrion18" name="[COLOR darkgreen]Atrion's Repo for Kodi 18.x[/COLOR]" version="0.6.3" provider-name="Atrion Darnay">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Atrions Repo">
            <info compressed="false">http://macarthurhouse.ddns.net/Kodi_18_Repo/_repo/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>http://macarthurhouse.ddns.net/Kodi_18_Repo/_repo/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">http://macarthurhouse.ddns.net/Kodi_18_Repo/_repo/</datadir>
            <hashes>false</hashes>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary>Atrion's Repo for Kodi 18.x</summary>
            <description>Atrion's Repo for Kodi 18.x</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="script.module.arrow"
       name="arrow"
       version="0.15.5"
       provider-name="crsmithdev, Razzeee">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.25.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.dateutil" version="2.8.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.backports.functools_lru_cache" version="1.5.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.module"
             library="lib" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en">Arrow: better dates and times for Python</summary>
    <description lang="en">Packed for Kodi from https://github.com/crsmithdev/arrow</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>Apache2</license>
    <source>https://github.com/Razzeee/script.module.arrow</source>
    <email>beenje AT gmail.com</email>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
